[Music]
hello and welcome to the junkyard love
podcast
at what age do we learn how to have
better conversations
at what age do we learn to have better
conversations with ourselves
[Music]
what's up my doodles this is jake and
welcome
to the junkyard love podcast the podcast
where every time before the episode
and the conversation gets going i drop a
little nugget of information or new
knowledge or thought-provoking
little thing or article or book or
audio clip today that audio clip is in
the form of
something i made myself with the help of
my friend
vance aussie he made this beat just on
his ipad for fun he sent it over to me i
slowed it down and sped it up i cut it
up i added some alan watts
vocal samples and samples from his
lectures
and kind of made a little storyline of
it and added uh some willy wonka bits
it's pretty fun so i hope you enjoy it i
hope it makes you think a little bit
um maybe eventually i'll throw it up on
my band camp
but anyway here's this episode drink
some dang water
sit down get comfy do your thing get
present wherever you're at
everybody take a big old deep belly
breath
enjoy the creation i made with my friend
vance
and then enjoy the episode with my
friend ricky
we're cheers
[Music]
not a speck of lighter showings so the
danger must've been grown
she was a bad egg
where'd she go where all the other bad
eggs go down the garbage chute
[Music]
[Applause]
so then when you die
you're not going to have to put up with
everlasting non-existence because that's
not an experience
a lot of people are afraid that when
they die
they're going to be locked up in a dark
room forever
and sort of undergo that
but one of the most interesting things
in the world this is a yoga this is a
way of realization
try and imagine what it will be like to
go to sleep and never wake up
[Music]
think about that it's one of the great
wonders of life
what will it be like to go to sleep and
never wake up
and if you think long enough about that
something will happen to you
you will find out among other things it
will pose
the next question to you what was it
like to wake up after having never gone
to sleep
that was when you were born
you you can't have an experience of
nothing nature reports a vacuum
so after you're dead the only thing that
can happen is the same experience
or the same sort of as when you were
born
[Music]
in other words we all know very well
that after people die
other people are born and they're all
you
only you can only experience it one at a
time
everybody is i you all know you're you
and wheresoever beings exist throughout
all galaxies it doesn't make any
difference
you are all of them and when they come
into being that's you coming into being
you know that very well
only you don't have to remember the past
in the same way you don't have to think
about how you work your thyroid gland
or whatever else it is in your organ you
don't have to know how to shine the sun
you just do it like you breathe
isn't it doesn't it really astonish you
that you are this fantastically complex
thing
and that you're doing all of this and
you never had any education in how to do
it
you never learned but you're this
miracle
well the point is that from a strictly
physical scientific standpoint
this organism is a continuous energy
with everything else that's going on
and if i am my foot i am the sun
how long does it take you to edit an
episode
once i actually sit down to edit it it's
probably like
it takes sometimes it literally takes
like six hours but it's because i'll
like let it play and i'll kind of like
walk around the room and i'll take some
notes i do it like in a very adhd manner
yeah
so um it takes me a while but a lot of
times it's like i don't edit it the day
of so sometimes i'll right now i have
three podcasts that i need to edit so i
sometimes i get like a little behind i'm
like okay i need to crank through this
one but
because i'm also when i edit them i'm
training my like
i'm trying to like learn as an audio
engineer and stuff too yeah and so i'm
like trying out different filters and
trying out like different um eqs and
stuff on people's voices like trying to
make people's voices i mean you're
talking gibberish to me right now but
amazing yeah i do that too yeah
but i think it's so cool like this stuff
is so hard
yeah it's i wanted to
like video is something that i want to
do um i don't have it set up now but
it's like
i was gonna wait till i had a video to
even start it but this podcast yeah
okay yeah my cousin does that he like
videotapes himself while he does his
podcast episodes
i like they talk about sports i'm like
wow yeah
i mean it's it adds this whole other
dynamic like i don't [__] know video
like i don't yeah i know audio like i
could figure out videos you know anybody
who does video
yeah i know a few friends who do video
um i was gonna say
yeah i mean i'm sure i can get somebody
to help me out with it i'm just kind of
at that point where i don't want to
make it too much on myself because then
i'll get behind like if that i'm like oh
gosh i have
six podcasts that i need to edit and
they're all video and i know that video
would take me longer than
than audio so it's something i'm working
towards i'm just not there yet
oh my god i'm the biggest procrastinator
so i get it
yeah i i just work on a bunch of [__] at
once like
i'm like oh i'm not working on that now
but i'm gonna get back around to it i
just have my
random wall over there just things i'm
half working on
at least you write it down yeah writing
it down is good
you're very organized you're like
inspiring me to be organized
are you not organized no i'm like living
i'm homeless
oh my god this is
yeah i'm homeless yeah i'm living out of
a suitcase you're such a bum i am a bum
yeah yeah i feel like i was telling you
um before so we're recording now by the
way if you didn't see
um i will actually pause that though so
you don't have to look at the
what you're so funny i don't care if i'm
looking at
anything i know that i am easily
distracted dude i have there's a window
behind your head
and i'm not kidding there will be birds
and squirrels that will distract me in
the middle of my conversation
oh yeah i'm so easily distracted yeah
actually but give you less things to
look at back here there's so many things
to look at in here
it's amazing yeah it's organized chaos
it is but yeah
hello ricky hall hello cheers from
across the table cheers i think people
can
clink yeah clink we're wearing masks too
what's your uh what's your view on the
masks i love the mask
you love the masks i love the mask i
hate how it separates up so much to me i
mean i know it gets so much more
complicated but to me it's like
that's fine just to wear it do you hate
the mask a little bit
i i i don't enjoy the mask
but i am someone who like if it's going
to help us it's going to help us feel
more comfortable around each other it's
going to help like
because i'm not working i could stay in
my basement right now and be fine but
like
there's people who are serving and
people who are like working in
supermarkets and like i don't want them
to be stressed out so i'm going to wear
a mask that's my opinion on it yeah
i mean i'm working at the coffee shop
right now and i have to wear one it's
hard
it's hard to wear it's hard to wear it
while you're working but at the same
time it does help me like not touch my
face
yeah that's true little stuff it does
make me feel more more safe
yeah it does it's like telling having
blankets on i know it doesn't
it doesn't help um you from getting it
but it helps stop the spread
but i'm like i feel i feel so much safer
yeah i mean it's it's a something like
it's such a pandemic is this
i mean it's a tiny virus that you can't
see like a virus is inherently scary
so it's just like if we can feel like
we're doing something to help ourselves
out a little bit
and to go out to restaurants and to have
you know those things open
yeah well what was the what was the
pandemic like for you like when it
so i mean how long has it been now it's
been like four months five months or
something since it was march i think
when everything shut down
yeah what was it like for you like what
were you doing in march it was so
bizarre i remember visiting home
in portland and i remember seeing on the
news and i was like talking to my cousin
cause i was staying at my cousin's house
and i was like is this something that we
need to worry about
i was like oh [__] like okay and he he
um is in afghanistan right now he's in
the military and so i i like trust
he's amazing so smart and like such a
badass and um he's like yeah like i
think we should worry about this
i was like well we'll think we'll see
yeah we'll see what everybody around me
yeah we'll see i'm like whatever like
you know there's something every year
and then i was trying
really hard to see my boyfriend in
canada while he was working over there
and i had
flown over there and that's when
everything shut down like sports
everything and i was like holy [__] that
was when it was like weird
yeah i was in a different country and i
was like am i
stuck here like holy [__] but
i don't know i i'm like scared of
everything anxiety central so
it scared me i'm still scared yeah i am
i mean it mine fluctuates up and down
like at the beginning i was super
terrified and i was like
oh my god i was i was avoiding news like
i was like oh like don't watch news it's
scaring me but i was
i was doing my own stupid research
though i was like i was
like as good as it is to avoid news i
would be like okay i do want to make
sure i know like some of the truth yeah
you want to educate yourself
sometimes i would just like dive deep
and hour on reddit and i'm like ah what
am i doing or like watching some
like because a lot of like more serious
people if you listen to their podcasts
like at the beginning they're like
get the [__] doors don't talk to
anybody don't open your amazon packages
and it's like yeah write down your food
from your grocery store and i'm like
okay like
cleansing everything like so nervous but
like oh
there's so many things that go into this
and like i'm not trying to bring up
politics but like some conservatives
you know still think it's fake and i'm
like there's people that are dying
and it's it's just it's a rabbit hole
yeah like on on
media wise it's a rabbit hole dude i
mean it's such a i mean
our town is is such a an interesting
like corner because we do have a lot of
like small town we have a lot of like
left and right and just very eccentric
different types of
yeah we're all over the place and like
seeing like you
um i mean we're not from the same town
are you from kalama or woodland i'm from
woodland woodland yeah so like
small towns kind of the same like area
we're a little far apart but i'd imagine
that on your facebook you have a pretty
bad person
you went to kelso yeah yeah high school
okay um
but it's just like just seeing so many
different types of different opinions
and seeing everybody argue it's just it
breaks my heart onto like it
i get angry sometimes and i'm like oh
you guys are being so stupid and then
i'm like but i don't even know
positive i'm the person that argues with
people and it's so unfortunate because
i'm like i get mad at myself i'm like
it's not worth it and then i'm like on
my facebook like arguing
because i feel so passionately about
right like equality right now like the
civil war
like there's gonna be like a civil war
everyone saying like the civil rights
movement
it's so important and like mass
yeah covet like trump i'm like this town
this is not the place for me right now
it's not i i think that i mean it sucks
to argue with people on facebook like
it's it's like that sentence just sucks
inherently but i do think it's good it's
a good time to stand up for something
like if you really think that you can
like help someone's perspective
or like get them to see something new
like i mean there's a lot of people that
like i worked at warehouses for five
years there's a lot of people in our
town that
haven't left callitz county ever and
that's that's not a bad thing that does
not make you dumb that doesn't make you
like
want a worse here yeah but you you have
also not really
been forced to question your perspective
very much and now with the internet
different perspectives are like thrown
at you in order to get outrage and
clicks
yep so we're just at like a growing
point with society and i just
to me it saddens me to see like small
towns
not connecting like we're we're getting
just a wedge thrown in
in us because of the news media and it's
really oh my god i was just
i was just looking up like 9 11
yesterday it was like this video and i
was
i was watching it and everyone's like it
was just so crazy how we came together
as a country
at a really like a crazy time and like
this one's dividing us
so hard like severely and it's
it's shocking like to me that this
isn't bringing us together other
countries like look at like
like canada new zealand australia like
they're like let's [__] let's beat this
[__] virus like let's
work together let's shut everything down
like honestly our government
trump specifically isn't helping
yeah and people don't realize and
they'll they'll like support him
like to their death and he's said so
many things and i'm like i don't if
obama said anything near
the things that he says i'm like so
that's what i'm saying like like it's so
simple like there's so many people who
are like how do you not see how
ridiculous it is but it's
it is so weird to me like what is
[__] i'm not saying it's just trump
either i don't know
but i know what you mean so because when
i say when i say trump too a lot of
times
i'm generalizing which sometimes you
have to do just to have conversation
right
when i say trump i'm like oh like trump
supporters i'm not trying to like
target specifically like people i'm not
saying all trump supporters are this way
or whatever yeah but it's kind of just
like a way of like carrying the
conversation to where you can
talk about kind of the people you know
that you're talking about like the there
is
you know with the people who are who
we're
arguing back against who are saying kind
of rude things
yeah um it's just i mean we're both on
both sides i guess yeah i know and there
there is two sides to everything even
the protests in portland there's two
sides
yeah rioting and vandalizing federal
buildings is horrible
there's always going to be that bad bad
egg and like a group
of course but if you actually look at
the protests they're peaceful
and then like these federal police
officers are coming in tear gassing
people yeah that's sketchy that's weird
shooting you with rubber bullets
like this is like illegal
yeah it's illegal and people like are
trying to support it but like
once trump violates the constitution
it's okay it's justified
but say obama did it it would be a whole
other conversation with
conservatives yeah it would be i got in
a fight with somebody last night about
it and i'm like
i think i don't know it's sad that we
have to fight for equality too
it's 20 20. yeah it's weird it's weird
to me i'm like wait what the hell is
going on
why is our simulation breaking down here
simulation oh my god a glitch
in the simulation i believe that i mean
everybody is turning against each other
in such insane ways and a lot of people
are like they care about the same things
they're just talking over each other's
heads they're like
arguing the wrong subjects but we're
just having an inability commit to
communicate and i think it's
a lot of like technology has just
changed [__] so much
that it's like really sparking us in
some ways do you remember the
first cell phone that you got yeah
it was like a nokia flip phone i think
was it a flip phone oh no it was a
samsung flip phone
or something like that no nokia nokia
weren't flip phones was there but was
there button because i'm trying because
there was even before like the slider
yeah there was a flip before this yeah i
just told you the time on the front it
flipped and then i remember i got a
razor
those were so sick they were so thin too
so they were they were the thinnest
thing
i was like oh my god everybody had a hot
pink razor i had i had male friends who
had hot pink razors like it was just
more popular you got them like
you like bought it off somebody or
something like my cheap ass spotted off
somebody i was like
you paid some chick to steal it from the
locker room yeah i'm like can i have
this put my sim card in it
i still have the same phone number from
like sixth grade i love that
oh epic i i feel like i had the i feel
like a lot of people actually keep the
same number now
it's more common but there was a while
where it's like oh you have 18 t and
you're switching to rise and you've got
to lose your number no
that was a thing i have to get a new
number when i go to canada i'm like
i've had this one forever oh i guess
that makes sense though
i could probably be more expensive yeah
i absolutely have to get a canadian plan
yeah i mean i okay so i i asked about i
always just like try to think of how
long it's been because it's
2007 was when the iphone came out like
not that long ago
and like think about how different our
lives are now and like completely
like controlled and ran and like
optimized in so many cool ways but like
also weird ways
by our phones and social media like it's
our phones run everything we've gone
through
a lot yeah and like when okay how old
were you when you got your razor
or or your your first phone to motorbike
i was in sixth grade how old are you in
sixth grade that's pretty old
or that that that was pretty young yeah
i remember when i got i got it for
christmas
and my mom was like this is for you
because i live with my grandpa and
they're like this is for you and your
grandpa to share my grandpa's like you
can [__] have it like
this i'm like yeah but i couldn't text
on it
like back then do you think that you
even wanted to text like was texting
even really a thing
i remember like we wanted to just
because like it would be funny
to say send a hay but it cost never cost
money yeah like each individual one
and then i remember i tried to buy like
a ringtone and my mom let me do it like
on my birthday and i bought like
shakira hipster lie oh my god this is so
cool
and then you're like trying to get your
friends to call you so you can just like
oh what's that song playing
it's from my pocket oh my god that's so
cool
why aren't ringtones like ring back
tones i always thought those were super
cool too
yeah i never did that i
i don't think i ever did it but i always
thought it was a cool idea and i kind of
wish that
our ringtones like okay i feel like
ringtones aren't really
that much of a thing now and like
there's those people who have like
nickelback or creed still somehow as
they're as the ringtone like there's
still those people but otherwise which i
think is really cool because
create a school i'm not i'm all bored
creepy okay
okay oh yeah it's just so weird how it
changes like do you have a ringtone
now or is it just the iphone it's just
the iphone one but god you're making me
want one
i know like what do we need what do we
need what song do we put on
okay if you had to choose a song right
now would it be a throwback
or i mean but also then you kind of get
into like shaylee has a couple ringtones
and she has like a couple like i have a
different one than megan and her mom has
a different one than
yeah um like me whatever but she only
has like four
but she's kind of like the only she's a
square i think you know she's like the
only one i know with the ringtone still
that's really cool i need to do that
she's yeah she's starting and she's
bringing it back all right if you have
to choose a ringtone right now top of
your head
god i'm just i think i'm in a really
depressed mood lately so i think i'm
like something billy joel
like okay okay yeah that's fine vienna
like that
oh my gosh dude okay so that song from
thirteen going on thirty
seven oh my god i love that movie
shaylee was watching it like a few
months back
or i mean it's probably been like a year
now but i was like kind of like
texting on my phone but kind of also
watching it because it's not that bad of
a movie
and then that song came on and i went
through like a stage of being super
obsessed i was doing like multiple times
a day oh my god
i heard it before but so mckenna my best
friend she
she got me on that song like i'm not
even thinking about that movie but she's
like she plays that song when she's all
depressed and like sad
and so we would listen to it in hawaii
all the time and we lived together and
she got me on it yeah and like it's so
good
i really like it i mean i've never like
explored him a ton but i think that he's
like he's one of like the master
keyboard players isn't it or like a
piano player
pretty sure yeah i think yeah i should
probably know that oh my god we're so
young no but yeah that's a great song
yeah so we need definitely a that or a
throwback for sure
yeah it'd be i don't know what mine
would be right now
i love queen too queen's the best
queen's like queen and fleetwood mac are
like my favorite bands
ever of all time yeah very nice what do
you remember like first getting into
from them like do you remember like
the first queen song or fluted mac song
you heard my dad was really into queen
and like we lived up in
ariel so he we always had a long drive
and he'd always play queen like over and
over again like from
age of five to like age 15. like just
queen
or aerosmith but my mom always listened
to fleetwood mac so i just like i think
it's just like nostalgic to like my
childhood
oh yeah so fleetwood mac yeah stevie
nicks my [__]
that's my [__] yeah i
it's interesting i always liked queen
but i was never like anytime someone
would be like obsessed with bohemian
rhapsody i'd be like
it seems like a long song so i didn't
get into it actually until the last
couple years i'm not kidding but like
i i feel like once i honestly this is
gonna sound corny as like someone who
should be on top of like queen like i
should be like
i'm a musician i should like have been
obsessed with them forever
the movie is what got me kind of like
more obsessed with them like
like with freddie i can say that like
yeah like
the elton john movie i had never
listened to that rocket man
yeah and then i started i was like oh my
god he's amazing and i had never
listened to his music before that and
then that one got me
hooked so i get it it sparked me more i
i
watched it on on a plane ride just like
oh i guess i'll watch this like i didn't
really think much of it and i was just
like see what this is just so pumped
i was wishing that someone was next to
me so i can make this did you see this
part it's cool like that part where
where he plays in that club and they
have like that cool part where his feet
are up off the ground
that's such a clever wonderful scene i
took my boyfriend to both of those
movies by the way
and i'm like crying at the queen at the
queen movie bohemian rhapsody i'm crying
because i'm like oh my god this is
amazing jack's like where the [__]
like you're so annoying drunk in the
theater i'm like this is amazing
you're just yelling yeah so excited it's
funny getting drunk in a movie theater
like there's still something
like when i was younger it's something
that i would do but there's still an
appeal of like being able to have a
drink or a beer or something oh my god
it's my favorite thing to do like
going to a movie theater is what i miss
the most right now i'm dying to go to a
movie theater
too getting like a little tipsy and
going to a movie
is the best thing on this planet yeah i
like getting a little stoned
yes except for like it's a it's a hard
situation because i'll just like smash
down a joint in the parking lot
like right when you right when you pull
in and then you got to go inside and pay
for your ticket and talk to the person
yeah you're like so you're like i'm
sorry that i'm incredibly stoned oh they
all know
yeah i mean you just smell like a damn
nug too yeah yeah
um so you've recently been well not
super recently but you've undertake
taken hockey you've uh
oh you've been thrown into the world of
hockey yes
what are you you're saying you weren't
like super you didn't know a ton about
it before but you have played sports and
stuff like what are some things that you
that you have noticed that you like
about hockey um i mean like going to the
games
is so exciting i only go like if jack's
playing obviously
um it's especially when you when someone
is playing that you love it's so
exciting that's gonna be intense oh my
god i'm like a hot mess
and i don't know yeah i
i couldn't tell you the rules
i don't think i know the rules yeah but
i yeah he i don't know
it's so exciting um just the atmosphere
just like going to like a blazer game
yeah yeah or like a seattle seahawks
game i haven't been to like a lot of
sports
events but they're exciting i love them
yeah it's like it's that
it's that energy like it's just
everybody's so excited to be there like
you don't have to be friends for the
same team
like yeah it's so funny and they're
talking [__] to each other which is like
yeah it's funny because i'm like i'm i'm
just like a feminine dude
i'm just like like those sports yeah i'm
like i'm in there i'm enjoying it but
i'm not someone who's gonna like
participate in the [__] talking oh my
god
yeah exactly yeah but it's it's fun to
like laugh at like everybody else doing
not at them but like with them you know
like it's just this different energy
it's really cool to be a part of it
if you just you would be surprised like
the fans
like are so serious it's shocking it's
amazing though it's beautiful
and i haven't gone to a toronto game yet
because he just he just got traded to
toronto and like la to toronto is going
to be very different la was different
like they were really big about the
lakers but like ellie king's games were
like
pretty intense but i just know canada's
extremely different
yeah definitely so i i don't even know
what that's like yet
so well that'll be an exciting new
venture hopefully you don't have to like
watch him get in fights and stuff i feel
like that'd be kind of goalies don't get
in fights so he's good he has his teeth
he's good to go yeah he's good the team
has his back so you're
like a golden retriever he's the nicest
person on the ice oh nice
the perfect be a goalie for him that for
him being a goalie yeah he's
very nice to even the other players that
are mean to him i'm like
dude that's i i played mini or mini
league uh
minor league baseball for like one year
when i was way younger and i remember it
being weird to people on my team
that i like i would like high five the
other players and [__] like
i didn't know i was like we're all
having fun i thought i didn't know that
was supposed to be like that's the end
of me i didn't know i was just so
yeah that's literally him and i'm like
do people chirp you on the ice like
people like
like skate up to you and he's like oh my
god they talk so much to you but then
they like
it's like a joke at the end they want to
like get you mad right like ruin your
game
yeah but man what it's a psychological
so it's kind of like
um it's not i'm not comparing it openly
as a sport but like so wwe kind of has
this like
those guys they're huge athletes like
they're actually that's actually like
hard like
like suplexing someone off a ring you
know it's an it's in
even if it's acting it's hard so but
it's but they're they're kind of in that
acting world
like they know like when they go
backstage i'm sure they kind of shut off
yeah they're like hey oh you did good
that was a good um
whatever like they know that they're
acting but when they're out there it's
like
we're we're on man and i feel like
hockey players kind of have that too
like it's not that they hate each other
it's like this is what you do in the
sport and many of these players have
like even on separate teams they played
together like growing up or like in
college or
even like when jack went to high school
they like practice play together
whatever
but like yeah when it's the game the
game's on they're so intense like
they're just giving each other [__] like
cussing like
it's a crazy sport yeah i think it's
impressive though like any
any athlete of any sport who can kind of
like
turn on that thing you know it's oh my
god it's like it's the action thing
starts
i have so much anxiety i'm like how do
you like people like
are so mean like screaming at you in the
stands
i'll be like in the family section and
people can sit in the family section
and they're like it's like saying [__]
you to like
certain players and i'm like oh my god
this is these i'm gonna say something
they're like on my like on the same team
and i'm like i know them personally like
holy [__]
i've never heard anyone say anything bad
about jack like in the stance before
thank god
but i would never say anything i'd be
like oh my god so embarrassing
you're just in the stands fighting on
his honor i know right gosh
it's just like uh sports oh so wild go
sports
go sports indeed it's a fun time to to
participate in it
i think it's i'm someone who like i just
can't help it i'm more paying attention
to like the
like oh what's that camera camera guy
doing on the corner there like on the
you know when you're watching football
or when you're watching sports i'm
always like interested in the whole
thing
oh my gosh we are the same person dude
for real
yeah you're just interested in like the
whole thing i always ask like stupid
questions i'm like god are the refs okay
like do they get beat up and he's like
yeah you hit all the time like oh my god
that's so sad
and like do they get paid well you're
just how's your color
doing in the middle he's like can you
keep your head in the game
i'm like how's your coach doing is he
okay is he good he seems pretty stressed
out he's yelling a lot
does he uh does he do yoga smiling yeah
oh my gosh
um so you guys are we were talking about
before the podcast you were having
trouble
getting into canada because coronavirus
is a weird thing and we're
our simulations yeah so so tell me about
this okay so
we'll back up a little bit um where
where all have you
you've lived in a few different places
yeah um so
you guys met um in hawaii
um but you've lived in l.a for a little
bit like tell me a little bit
a little bit about that like what the
places that you have lived and then
what's going on with you getting into
canada well we only knew each other for
four months when i moved to la
which was insane but going back and
forth which is super expensive
from maui to la so i made like the
ultimate decision to move to la
um we were there for about a year and a
half
and he he resigned with the la kings
and he was like there's no way we always
talk to i'm like
it's so expensive here like california's
crazy it's beautiful but it was just
like so expensive
i'm like it would be so funny like or
fun if you got traded
and like he's like there's no way like
we i just resigned like we're not gonna
get traded we're gonna be here for
like years i was like okay like this is
my life now this is where i live
california is it
right and i was visiting home i was in
portland
and he calls me and he's like oh my god
i think i'm getting traded and i was
like to where and he was like i think to
toronto i was like holy [__]
okay and i was like no we didn't hear
anything three days go by
he gets traded like it's in a second so
he has to leave like the next day
what yeah and like i'm in california
well i was in portland but i live in
california we had like animals
so i'm like holy [__] like what are we
gonna do i was in school at the time and
i'm like
um so i'm not gonna see him for a while
whatever we figured it out
he it was our situation so unique
because corona happened at the same time
yeah and so he was in canada on a work
visa i had
i was visiting him at the time corona
was happening we had to go back to la to
pack up our stuff
and ship it to toronto they're like
jack can only come because he's they
want he's the only one on like has a
work visa like he can only come here
and they're like unless you guys want to
sign a marriage certificate you must
think well
like getting forced into it from yeah we
want to do it the right way of course
um uh yeah so we're like there has to be
like a loophole
whatever we have a lawyer you know he
thinks he knows a way
so wow dude what a complicated thing
like what
who would have thought that like all my
stuff is there
we have a house like i live there my my
aunt my animal was there like
we live there it's i'm like the only i'm
just stuck
and like as soon as i get there if i say
i get in there like i'm never gonna want
to leave
until this is completely over yeah i
mean what's that even mean like what's
completely over even mean at this point
like when are we going back to normal
i know it's so this is the new normal
the new normal
mask everyone's just like americans are
just crazy and don't let them in your
country
oh god we're struggling
we're losing our minds a little bit just
have a little patience we're still the
leaders of the free world
yeah don't don't do what we're doing
though yeah don't do it
yeah um okay so before that you lived in
okay you lived in hawaii for a while
though right mm-hmm tell me about hawaii
i want them
oh my god everything i ever dreamed
about because i've never been so sell me
on it like what's the you need to go
it's i need to sell you okay well it's
i mean like i could never live in a city
okay i'm like such a small town girl
like
always forever but i
like the island vibe is everything
i've ever wanted it's just like a small
town
everyone's family and i fit in so well
in maui like
even getting a job that i my favorite
job i've ever had
like a job i actually enjoyed and like
everyone there
i i feel we always joke it's like the
black sheep
of your family that moves to maui like
everyone's a black sheep and we all like
the black sheep my family yeah same i'm
the black sheep and like everyone just
like fits and it's it's so beautiful i
caught i love it i mean everyone dates
the same person
but it's like the dating pool was really
shitty but
i like i loved it it's something i wanna
like i wanna die there
you're gonna go there just to die this
would be like i mean i wanna grow old
and die in there
of course but i want to go we've been to
um
we've been to the caribbean twice we've
been in jamaica and um cayman island
we came in grand cayman that was such a
wonderful place and that was the first
time i had gone to like any sort of
like exotic like beach beachy place like
that
so that was pretty crazy but i could you
do you like think you could live there
if you had to
i i think now when i had gone there i
just loved it and i don't think i could
live there
but now i'm like such a [__] hippie
that i think that i would really it
would be easy yeah
i would i would i would enjoy it that's
how i'm like i was kind of nervous
everyone's like you get island fever
i'm like okay because my family lives in
maui like my family part of my family
lives
um two hours away from where i was
living but she hadn't
she was getting island fever at my when
she was my age and i was like well
if i if i get it i can always move away
whatever and like i wasn't there long
so i'm i just don't really see myself
getting that
you don't think you'll get eye on the
favorite so like so an island fever is
where you're
just like i gotta get off this dress
yeah yeah you're stuck and like you do
go to the same places you go to the same
bars like
maui is so small there's like one
nightclub it's like
to go there as a young person it's
hilarious because
your friend visit you and you're like
what are we going to do tonight and
you're like well
we're going to go to the dirty monkey is
it called the dirty monkey
of course it's called the dirty moment
or down the hatch that's like that's
like the west side
best bar yeah but that's what you do
it's like the same things
i mean that's kind of what you do in
your hometown too i know right but like
i love visiting and going to like the
cool bars here
like where all your friends will be yeah
it's nice running into your old friend
it's funny because you go through a
stage of like
like i mean it's i guess different for
me because i'm always in bars working in
them
but like you go through a stage of like
i i don't want to see people that i
like if i haven't seen them since high
school there's a reason why like you
have those stories like catch phrases
that you'll say and then you kind of get
older you're like you know [__] it is
kind of good to run into that guy or
that
yeah it's good yeah definitely some
people yeah i mean yeah there's some
that's that's not so great to run into
i this is so funny that you bring this
up because i like
i have so many friends on my facebook
like from high school
the people that i never hung out with in
high school like post things that i
relate to
and i was like oh my god like i'm not
saying i was hanging out with the wrong
group
but like i just there's a lot of people
that
like i wish i would have hung out with
and then i see around town and i'm like
really excited to see them
that's good yeah yeah that is that is
something cool that social media offers
us like
yeah like you get to see the best i mean
not always but
different sides of people rather like
you get of kind of i mean that's what it
is it creates a community
like it's it's we've never had it so i
read this reddit comment
um uh not so long ago and somebody
essentially had asked the post was
high schoolers now of um who are in high
school now in 2020
i think this was before the pandemic um
but
they said like what's something that
older people probably wouldn't really be
able to understand or believe about high
school
and they said um there's not really
clicks like there's not really like
everybody's kind of like cool with
everybody but like
who you like is is on your phone like
you talk to the people who you like on
your phone you connect with people
like your community through your social
medias and stuff and then
like in physical person you're like
you're quite cool with people
everybody yeah but i feel like people's
main interactions is probably more on
their phone
than oh yeah yeah so that's like an
interesting thing
so weird but but i i mean it would be
cool to
you know because i had so many friends
growing up like like
yeah i feel like i got along with a lot
of people but i i never
like there it took me a while to find
people you know where i'm like oh you're
so much like me we have the same
interest
you know yeah and i feel like maybe kids
are able to cut that and they're like
able to get people who are
just like them right away or i know yeah
i mean like i definitely feel like
when we were in high school when did you
graduate 2010 wasn't ten yeah i feel
like it was clicky
yeah like the time it was yeah like i i
probably like
didn't have a lot in common with the
people i hung out with but or like i
wanted to be cool i partied
like stupid stuff that i probably
wouldn't have done like really
right i don't know just like i love a
party but
just so like the atmosphere i put myself
into i'm just totally different
from today so right i mean that's that's
the thing too is
as you grow older you know especially if
you start traveling different places you
see
you meet different types of people and
stuff you realize like how much you do
change
like i feel like the i know i always say
people never change what you really do
yeah you do people change i've always
said that though like people don't
change
but they do so that's the sour way to
look at it i mean it's easy i was sour
when i was younger
right yeah i feel it i mean i changed
exactly so that's exactly what happened
um so i wanted to talk to you
about your breast implant situation um
i like i just want to leave the door
open to you for you to talk about it
how you would like to talk about it i
know that it was a whole debacle for you
the whole thing we talked briefly about
it so um
i mean like i don't want to come at it
at like as a negative thing
because i think plastic surgery can be
beautiful like i get botox i get fillers
things like that
um but like going under the knife and
making the decision to put
something foreign in my body was really
devastating
right on both my mental health and just
my body yeah that was the that was a
strange thing to me just because i mean
i guess i don't know anything about it
but that it affected your mental health
so much like that's so that's so intense
so okay give me
um well give listeners rather a low down
of like what like what went on they
don't know if they've never heard of
any of the situation well when was it
i decided to give breast implants i had
no idea i wanted them it was like a
split
second of me deciding i wanted to get
implants i was like oh
well i remember i was like kind of
thicker in high school not thick like i
wasn't fat by any means but i was
um athletic i was playing a lot of
sports and then i remember
graduating high school and i was running
a lot
um and like i lost weight really easily
and i thinned out like really fast
lost all the muscle and like the first
thing that went with my breasts
and i was like oh my god like why do i
have such small boobs
and um i was talking to somebody
like my co-worker at the coffee shop i
worked at and she had breast implants
and she's like i love them
my sister had them i'm like okay yeah
that's an option for me
i wanted to see like how much money it
was wasn't too expensive
i was like i can do this like i
and i went in for my consultation and
you know he gives you like things to try
on
like what options you have and he was
like we have this new
implant it's called the gummy bear
implant it's textured on the outside so
it's like fits to your skin
so it looks more natural i was like wow
like this is exciting like it's new
yeah and like i felt it's like it felt
like a gummy bear i was like it's so
textured and cool
like let's do it he's like i can get you
in in two months
and i was like oh my god really like
he's like yeah i had a cancellation so i
really had no time to think about it
and then i remember i went on like a
vacation with my boyfriend at the time
and like a couple and my my friend she
was like you really shouldn't do this
like you haven't had much time to think
about it
and i was like oh my god somebody that's
actually like don't do it because
everyone
shout out to your friend for like saying
oh my god hello
she yeah she was like you ha you don't
have a lot of time to think about it
and i like looking back now i was like i
didn't
and i was like it's gonna be great like
it's gonna feel good whatever
my body is so sensitive to everything i
didn't
i didn't even like look that up like
this has been happening since the 90s
women have been complaining about like
feeling sick from foreign objects in
their body
what's that thing they get like when you
have like heart palpitations they get
like um
do you know what i'm talking about
dysrhythmia yes and they get like a
device put in their heart oh um
i forget what they're called but people
complain about having
like they get sick from having that in
their body because it builds scar tissue
around
oh wow yeah but i'm like i read about
that and i was like
can't be similar my sister has them like
i'll be fine yeah and your sister was
fine
she didn't have any of these yeah she
got them she's 10 years older than me so
she got them
so long ago when she was 20 and she
feels completely fine
but like i'm sensitive to like certain
like lotion i'm
like i'm allergic to latex and like
certain
just like fragrances like i'm didn't
even think about that
i get the surgery i love them they're
beautiful
whatever um i didn't even start noticing
my dad had died obviously into
2013 and i think that
like really upset my i or you're like um
started my anxiety
right um
but i don't know like you didn't really
have much anxiety before
like of course you went through so this
is confusing so like i had my dad died
in 2013. i got my breath in place in
2015.
i thought the anxiety started when my
dad died
and like i was like maybe i had anxiety
from that but i didn't start noticing
like physical symptoms
until my breast implants so i would get
like
there's like there's so many symptoms i
would get i'd be like tingling in my
arms and fingers the tea i had
definitely like definitely had fatigue
um like severe eczema psoriasis
losing my hair things like that what
um oh my god i have a note let me look
at my symptoms like all the symptoms you
took them down
yeah so were you like going through it
for a while like was it
just they started adding years after i
got them in like the implants in
yeah and like because it's hard to
correlate that like you probably
wouldn't ever
like think like yeah and i was like
maybe i'm just like getting older i was
like is this like something of me
getting older heart palpitations i had
chest tightness
shallow breathing like i felt tight like
heavy on my chest
um i would get like blurry vision i was
like i'm losing my sight cause i'm
getting old i really need to get glasses
like i would just like justify
everything
sensitive sensitivity to touch dry scalp
like
um i was gaining weight and i had the
same
like i've always had the same diet
exercise routine
so that was kind of confusing um so they
finally ended up putting me on
um like an antidepressant i was like
well i'm not depressed
i'm like well it helps with anxiety i
was like okay like we'll see how this
goes
i'm still on it today which i do think
it helps but
i started googling like what could be
wrong with me because i went to a doctor
and
she took like my blood test she did a
chest x-ray
like um an ekg because i was having the
heart palpitations and
she it was it was his doctor in
california
and she was a friend from the team jack
played for and she's amazing i love her
but she was like you're so healthy like
your blood test came back and you're so
healthy
and i was like okay like i i remember
getting the call and i was like kind of
crying because i was like
i don't feel good no you don't have
answers explain it yeah like i'm so
sorry about like i don't feel good and
she was like
well like you should go see like a
doctor about your breast implants
and like everyone in california was so
like expensive
like that like i was like i kind of want
them out just like to get them out i
wasn't even thinking
like anything about the implant that was
in i was like i just want them out
and they were like they quoted me like
25 000 or some [__] to take them out
yeah i was like i [__] i can't afford
that so
um they're like you're gonna hate what
you look like like they're
they're gonna be really saggy and gross
like you're not gonna like them
like i'm a guy and i know what breasts
are supposed to look like and like this
is like that's a weird sentence oh my
god so many doctors in california are so
bizarre and they were like this is what
you want
i was like well it's not what i want
like i don't feel good it's attacking me
i know and then i was like you you like
you ask yourself you're like is this
like in my head am i just is this just
severe anxiety
right do i have that could be so
confusing so eventually i put on
an anti-anxiety which is like a sedative
and like god it
you take it and like you can't drive on
it you can't like do anything like you
feel high
and you feel like oh my god like this
isn't how i want to like live my life
it just got so bad i couldn't get out of
bed some days because i was so ill
oh man like i would get up and i would
like pass out
or like hyperventilate to the point
where like i had to call 9-1-1 there's
been like four instances like when i had
to like
go see a dog i think this was a combo of
obviously how you were feeling but also
anxiety yeah a combo of like was this
when you were taking the anxiety
medication too
yeah okay yeah i think everything
everything of like a mix like they're
trying to like help me
my breast implants like just the thought
of having like this toxic bag in my
chest
and like and then i started googling and
stuff and everyone's like okay
there's this rare type of lymphoma like
this rare cancer of the immune system
that's like killing women
and i was like what's it linked to the
breast implants that i have
and i was like holy [__] [__] i was
like oh my god it's like they um
recalled them in europe which they came
from europe
and then um they haven't they hadn't
been recalled in the u.s
yet so i called my doctor and i was like
kind of scared i was like oh my god holy
[__]
like what do i do and he was like if you
feel like
you're sick like i want to see you type
thing yeah
because i had seen the doctors in
california and they didn't want to do
the explant or they were really
expensive
so i went home to portland and he was
like if you want him out like i'll take
him out he's like this oh my god
he's the best doctor i've ever had in my
life and he's the one who
charged me nothing yeah put him in oh
wow
so he took him out for free well he took
him out for free but i had to pay like
the
um surgical room fee and like yeah
um it cost me like nothing and he
even asked me if i wanted to put
different implants in because he would
do it for free he was like
i want you to feel comfortable whatever
but i had gotten
they they finally got recalled let me
backtrack a little bit they got recalled
in
the summer of 2000 last summer 2019.
i had i gotten a letter from my doctor
like these are recalled
they don't suggest you get them taken
out unless you have these symptoms
it was like swelling pain and redness of
the breast
and i had like the swelling and the pain
severe pain in my left breast like i
couldn't sleep at night like i would cry
like if like jack had touched my boob
like it like hurt
couldn't breathe i was like oh my god
i'm gonna get them taken out
whatever and i [__] you not
as soon as i woke up from my surgery i
like could breathe
i'm like holy [__] [__] i felt like
so
i don't know like if i don't know if
it's a placebo like it's in my head yeah
hey
it could have been i mean even if it is
i'm like
well i mean what our brain believes i i
feel like you know your intuition was
probably like hey
this is a problem like whether or not
the information you looked up like
fed to that but it seems like even
before that you were like i want to get
these out they're not something is wrong
you have that like intuitive feeling so
i know and then i know a woman who
um had them got them removed and got new
implants and she does feel better
she says but like even my sister she
feels good with her implants like
she feels fine like some people probably
can't have them and feel completely fine
but i just feel like some some bodies
can't
have that foreign object in your body we
create a scar capsule around the implant
to protect ourselves
from this foreign object and when they
took it out
i wanted the scar capsule out because
that's where the cancer is found is in
the scar capsule
yeah and so i was like i want it all
scraped out and like i was like i wanted
proof
like take a photo please just for my
like state of mind right
um yeah and he like took the photo i saw
the implants the scar
tissue everything and then i think this
is what people need to be aware of i
was starting to feel like scar tissue
like hardness
i was like it's car tissue because my
mom has had surgery i know what scar
tissue is like it just hardens
like what's it like calcifies or
something i have no idea
i'm not smart enough to know that but um
there was like a lump in my left breast
the problem breasts that i had and
um i didn't i was in california i was
like obviously corona was happening i
wasn't thinking about it i was like
it'll go away or like it's probably what
i have to live with
whatever like i do feel better i felt
amazing smarts like
like 20 of my symptoms have disappeared
i still have like the anxiety
but it's 90 better
that's great that's great um and then i
i was like well i'm here i want to like
have him look at my
scar tissue or this lump that i have in
my breast i went in like two weeks ago
and he was like how long have you had
this and i was like probably since the
surgery which was in
the end of january like beginning of
february and he was like
you have like fluid buildup in here
which could cause an infection like
serious infection
it's like holy [__] okay and he like
laid me down like um
got like he like put a needle in me got
all the fluid out
and he was like you just like have to be
i have to keep seeing you until like we
make sure like you're not getting any
more fluid build up like how severe it
could have been
yeah i was like holy [__] yeah so what
what is the cause of the fluid buildup
is it well when you
when you get the cert when you get an
excellent surgery you have to have like
drains
i don't know like that i don't know the
medical term but like it just builds
it's just like gunk pretty much yeah it
just builds up in there builds up and
like it's draining
like all this like blood like nasty
stuff um
i get i probably should have the drains
in longer than i did
but i hadn't been for like two weeks
which is like normal but yeah my left
breast just like didn't get all the
stuff out
i guess i don't know but it was just
scary so you're still healing from it
you know you're still your body
still yeah you said it would be a year
like probably
to fully heal oh my god when i like
first saw them like after surgery i was
like they're so ugly i was like crying
like now they're like my 20 year old
self like oh you're fine with it like
it doesn't affect you no like i was
young enough to like get them taken out
so like if everyone like if anyone's
ever worried
like you're young enough like your skin
he's like your skin didn't thin out
like your skin's healthy and yeah i had
big implants in
i went really large what size did you
have i had 400 cc's
which was like a triple d at the
beginning and i was like a double d yeah
by the end when they settled
okay yeah yeah that's that's super crazy
so did you
because i know you were doing a lot of
pilates stuff did you get into pilates
kind of like
after that like like um i asked because
i
i had um i'm just curious so
uh so for me with yoga like i've been
working out my whole life i don't know
if this is super related but i've been
working out my whole life
i've been a skateboarder like i've
always been active but like i didn't
until i was like 25
26 started doing yoga 27 whatever it was
um
i like this like connection to my body
um started like
forming that i like so hard to explain
and it just sounds like
totally woo-woo in every way but i get
it yeah so
do you have anything similar to this at
all like like after or like a you know i
started pilates
this is really weird i had nothing going
on in l.a because like when i moved
there
i um like i i didn't i didn't really
want to like get a job right away just
because i didn't know anybody
um and jack did pilates and i met this
woman who
was his pilates instructor and she just
got me hooked to it but
when i was doing it i felt like
pain obviously and that's another reason
why i drove me to get them out
um but no i get what you're saying
yeah it's euphoric like it's you have to
feel connected to your body
yeah it's like what you should be doing
so so what do you feel about your
like what what it what has been
something ringing in your mind about
your connection to your body now like is
it do you do you
think that you do you feel different
with your body like is your connection
your body different than it was before
you started
so much different like i i didn't like
it's so funny because
you think like if you like you fix
yourself you get bigger boobs you're
like oh my god i'm gonna love myself
more
like i didn't i love myself less i
didn't feel good i'm like i hate my body
it's so just like i hate you for feeling
so ill like it was fighting to like stay
alive
yeah it was helping you out it was like
hey oh my god you're so sick and like
now like now when i work out i haven't
been able to run and like i was used to
be like a runner
i haven't been able to run for like
years because i never i never ran in
hawaii it's too hot but like
now like being able to run like it feels
good
and like even doing pilates and like
things like that like
it's like it feels healthy like i'm
helping my body and
i love my body now i feel more youthful
i feel like that's
that's good yeah i'm gonna cry this is
so emotional
it is it's so sad because like god girls
like feel like they need to have stuff
like that
yeah yeah like i love plastic surgery
i'm not gonna like dog on it but
some things we can't have yeah and i
feel like a lot of
you don't need it like unless it's you
know it's it's of course it's your own
choice
it's always your own choice but you know
it's a lot of times we do things because
yeah i i mean look at you you're like
you're like i'm gonna do this thing and
i'll like my body more
but it's almost kind of like this weird
like confused image a little bit where
you know for me like i used to work out
and i would just be like big i just want
to be big and like for me it was kind of
my protective like i was like trying to
build that
scar to protect my armor you know like
yeah to protect that little boy that was
still hidden in there you know
but i don't know man the connection to
my body
is so much more important than like what
i think other people think when they see
my body
you know it's this new we should work
out to like feel better about ourselves
like i work out to like eat what i want
and like feel confident whatever
but we shouldn't have this like really
unhealthy relationship with working out
like
changing our bodies getting plastic
surgery like we
it's it's a weird world we live in right
now yeah it is
instagram is like honestly really i
understand like going on my popular page
i'm like holy [__] i wish i looked like
that like
wow of course and like i look back and
i'm like that girl has fake boobs like
because they look so nice like
oh i wish i still had mine and then i'm
like stopping myself i'm like no you
don't
like yeah you don't yeah why would you
want that like you didn't feel good
it's so it's so easy to like that like
because i get it too like i mean even
there's sometimes where i'll notice
like because i was i mean i was i was
like chunky towards the end i was like a
big boy i was strong but i was like
204. but like i'm i'm like 160 now or
something
and like sometimes i'll literally look
like on instagram you'll see like a
streetwear page or something and
somebody's yoked and i'm like oh man
his shirt just looks way dope in 60
pounds yeah and like and i'll catch
myself doing that my question
you look so healthy you look great by
the way thank you thank you i appreciate
that you do too you look fantastic yeah
thank you
it's good to be healthy it's good to
have that connection with our body
i'm always trying to tell people i'm
always like you know
yelling on my on my social medias and on
here like
the connection that we have to working
out has always been this i need to lose
weight
oh i got a vacation coming up or oh i've
got i
i hate my body now and i want to not
hate it and it's like
you don't approach it from that like
what it should be is like wherever
you're at doesn't matter however you
feel about like oh i'm overweight or i'm
underweight or i want more muscle or i
have too much muscle whatever it is yeah
it should be like going to the gym or
stretching or
doing pilates or doing yoga any of these
things should be to like explore your
body like you have to learn about it
make you happier
yeah i know i feel like when i was
younger like
with my implants i felt like i kept like
i was working out to like
look a certain way and i was never
satisfied
like i just come to realize that like
like am i ever going to be satisfied
like no just like love your body for
what it is like
you know yeah of course like everyone's
like yeah i love like what god gave you
whatever
but like you really have to find
like that healthy relationship with how
you look and
what you eat and how you want to treat
yourself and your body and your mind and
everything it's
and it's an ever-growing like there's a
learning just by getting older but we're
also like with
with technology and like advancements
and like all everybody learns something
new like every day there's something new
about our health or about food that we
love every year and so we're always like
you kind of just gotta
yeah you gotta like try to watch out for
the fads and try to just like eat
something
and then how does that feel to your body
like oh it doesn't feel good well you
know maybe
eat that once a week or don't eat that
or you know you gotta like
we're always stumbling into what feels
really healthy but also have like a
[__] cheeseburger and
some french fries i don't know and live
life yeah have a beer
yeah i i try to do um i try to when i'm
at home i try to eat healthy like so
my first two meals when i break my fast
are healthy and then like if i'm out
um like at a brewery or something it's
like oh get a beer of course
and then i'll get all since i ate the
other two meals
healthy i'll be like oh it's fine too
yeah oh yeah if i eat healthy all day
i'm like i can have like a really
fun dinner for sure you got to like kind
of work with your mind on that stuff
like we get so hard on ourselves
and we kind of all this [__] is sold to
us in so many ways
like we got to find our own
individual connection with health in our
own bodies
it's just so important i was talking
with so i actually had
you're the second ricky that i've had on
the podcast this week yeah i had
a uh my mind uh it's he
it's a male and this is r-i-c-k-y
um ricky nevereddy is his name he's over
a couple days ago and he's a power
lifter
um and we were talking about because i
said when i was younger i used to lift
with them
um and that was like so cool like these
like power lifters big ass dudes like
and of course when you're lifting with
power lifters you're gonna try to be a
power lifter
so that's all lift in and we started
getting in um
he was using the word ego lifting and i
was like i really liked it i was like oh
that's what i was doing like
this ego lifting i loved going to the
gym to
um and i wasn't fully conscious of this
like this was like kind of a protection
i was like really depressed trying to
like figure my own brain out but like
i would go into the gym and work out
super hard and
look big like get a pump like a drink
pre-workout before like get that pump
like look big feel big oh my shirt's
tight again against my arm
i'm good to go and like that would be my
workouts a lot of the times
like just trying to feel good in the
mirror before i leave the gym
and then it's like you're staring at
yourself in the mirror and like people
get off on that like at the
when you go to a gym like even like
women like we're like you know
lifting weights we like love looking at
us looking at ourselves lifting weights
and working out
it helps the workout and i get exactly
yeah i understand exactly what you're
saying
and that's like that's i feel like
that's a little bit unhealthy
yeah no it totally is as someone who's
done it himself it's unhealthy it's
there's a lot like you you gotta look
you know you're looking in the mirror
you're getting your posture down
but if it does help you finish a workout
i'm like okay oh yeah
yeah you need to work out like a workout
is great for you but
no i know exactly what you're saying i
think being more aware of my thoughts
though it's less of like
like but if it was helping at the time
then like
if it mentally yeah i mean you have to
do what makes you feel good yeah you're
only honest
meditating working out yeah if it's
getting you those endorphins like
i don't know i [__] hate running like
hate running with all of my heart
but like i know afterwards i feel so
mentally stable i'm like oh my god i
feel so much better like i can go out
and hang out my friends without stress
yeah if i go on a run dude run running
is everything i have to like
i feel like it's getting the energy out
i know like yeah it is
how do you feel okay like halfway
through on your run do you still hate it
oh my [__] hate
you hate every second i mean like you
get that runner's high eventually like
some run
runs are different than others like i
used to like
run like what was it like nine miles a
day i was like that was when i
before my surgery when i was losing a
bunch of weight and my sister got i hate
running and you ran nine miles a day
because like i wanted to be thin and
like that was like the easiest way to
lose weight
and like because i thought i was like
fat in high school i was [__] i was
[__] up
and i wasn't fat i was just athletic and
i lost
so much weight by running and like i got
that runner's high doing those like
eight seven mile and nine mile runs but
um yeah like in between like you get
that that runner's high and you know
we're not really thinking about it but
afterwards like mentally i was probably
like probably like the happiest i've
ever been right
like before my implants like i was happy
yeah stable like mentally i feel pretty
savage after a long run oh my god you're
like
i'm cool yeah i ran a long time i'm cool
i always like
for me it's always uh not always but a
lot of my runs
are sometimes i will run because i have
to fight mr hyde that sounds kind of
crazy but like
a lot of times i'll be like in a bad bad
place or like a depression day or
something
and i'll go for a run you know like you
just kind of have those bad thoughts
like just intrusive thoughts coming up
sad thoughts would it like oh my god
intrusive thoughts i i google this all
the time they're real
oh they're very i talk to them with my
counselor all the time it's a form of
ocd and i have that
yeah you do dude okay so so what what
have you learned about intrusive
thoughts like
and like okay this is gonna sound crazy
but like like when the bad thoughts come
in
we have good thoughts right when the bad
thoughts come in we like overanalyze
them because we're like why are these
bad thoughts here but one of the good
thoughts right we don't even think about
it
so intrusive thoughts like if you're
driving down the road and you're like
what if i just
yeah what if i just murder that yeah
yeah
like what if i'm holding a baby what if
i just like [__] drop it yep why
do we have those thoughts it's [__]
real it's a form of ocd and i have that
and i got yeah yeah i've i've read a lot
of
anxiety books about it because it scared
me at first i'm like
[__] like of course i don't want to
run my car off the [__] road
right but we're scared that we're going
to do it yeah like we're not in control
of our mind
and people don't realize that and like
people are too scared to talk about it
yeah i mean me and jason i talk about
this all the time dude it's like
it's so real people don't want to talk
about intrusive thoughts and like
it's it's a disease and like it takes
over your mind and like people need to
talk about it because like
a lot of people have it i think a ton of
people have it i had it super bad and i
didn't understand i didn't have the
intellect i didn't have the knowledge
because you're too aware you're too
aware and people with anxiety are too
aware
of life i swear i know i wish i could
just check out sometimes
we're way too well like it's cool to
have anxiety now you're like you're more
weak if you have anxiety
yeah but yeah like no we're just too
aware of being alive and
it's like like we the good thoughts
we don't even realize when we're having
the good thoughts of bad thoughts we get
we over analyze and it's really scary so
what did you
do you remember like you remember the
first time you started like feeling bad
about having an intrusive thought like
like if you're like driving out
you're driving over a bridge and you
like think about like i could turn my
wheel
left and just murder that family in that
van like you have that thought and then
you're like oh what the [__] is wrong
with me
oh my god i didn't start thinking about
like dark stuff like that until like
after my dad died i had
nothing traumatic has ever happened to
me until my dad died and
like his death was so
like quick and such an accident that
i was like oh my god bad things can
happen i think yeah that's like when my
anxiety kicked in
and like i didn't the intrusive thoughts
didn't come in
until i moved to hawaii actually yeah i
was like why am i thinking this way
i was like that's really weird like oh
my god this is
you might have to edit this out we'll
edit it out if we have to this is so
weird
um but like if you ever like sometimes
i'm like holding a knife and i'm like
what if i just
what if i just did that that is not that
weird i'm not going to say
am i weird so i don't talk about all the
time i've literally had i've had this
exact conversation with my counselor
actually
i so i was like i literally
like every time i would cut a knife or
use a knife i would literally
be it started to become afraid of it so
like when i got farther and farther
towards like
your mind you're afraid of it because
your mind's afraid of it
it creates this conundrum too when you
start like thinking that that thought's
you
like you're like i i don't trust myself
to like fold anybody's knife and it's
like i'm definitely not holding
anybody's baby if they hand it to me
tomorrow like
well and then you think about like what
if i dropped them on accident or if i
even just threw it right even a bunch of
things like you do think of the worst
things possible like what if i hurt
their kid or
what if i like ran somebody over on
accident or what if i
like i don't know you think about even
things that you're not in control of
like it's yeah you're not your thoughts
though okay so what do you okay so say
say
there's a young listener who is
experiencing intrusive thoughts and
they're like cool [__] i didn't know
that other people have these i don't
know we're allowed to talk about them
and they're listening to us
oh my god it's a form of ocd and
everybody has it yeah and you're fine
and you're not your thoughts
but some people don't have it like some
people have like they don't have like
they don't have it no but
it's okay like you're not gonna hurt
somebody you're not gonna make those
things because you're aware of it you're
not gonna do it yeah because you don't
want to like
you're so afraid that you're gonna do it
you know you're not gonna do it at the
same time think about the reason why you
feel bad about it it's because you know
that it's not
not right you're not gonna do it [__]
also i i watch like so much true crime
[__] i think i'm afraid of like the
consequences of like doing something
horrible and like i can't even
fathom how people do that to other
people that like i'm so afraid that like
i would be in that circumstance
right or like somebody's gonna hurt me i
have that fear too that like
we don't know people the people that we
fall in love with people that we're
friends with like we don't know our
neighbors
and like i have that fear also i'm
afraid of everything dude
like okay so so i have a similar fear um
and this is one that i still
that i still struggle with but i never
give in to it anymore like i
i have like i don't let my mind take me
there so
um and in it i think it's similar so
my upbringing when i was younger i had
to like stay
at my friend's houses like their parents
would keep me for four days or whatever
and like i was staying with my friend
right you're just hanging out your
friend's house
but like i knew it's because like things
weren't going good at home i didn't have
like a place to stay like i had like
stay with them
and so i started like seeing my
friendships as like oh you're just
friends with me because your parents
made you be friends with me and i
started like
questioning every relationship and
friendship that i had and it like
polluted my mind
and it was like those were literally my
friends they liked hanging out with me i
had we had great times together like i
happened to have a situation at home
where i stayed with them for longer than
a lot of other people yeah but it's it
like i would grow up
and you start like it'll be a sudden
thing like you're really good friends
with someone you connect with them you
you're like it's a flow state when
you're talking to them you love them
you're just talking from your stomach
and then suddenly you have that thought
of like dude you made this whole
situation up
this guy who doesn't really like you
that much i know i've never had that
oh you've never had that no oh well
hopefully it doesn't populate in your
head now oh my god i'm just kidding
no but like nobody's no i understand
what you're saying though because like
you're you're like sabotaging their
relationship yeah
so if even like when you're talking to
like your partner
you're like you're like so okay so say
like you have this like intuition that
you don't trust your partner right
you're sabotaging the relationship by
making things up in your head i've had
dreams where like i'm like okay
my boyfriend's cheating on me like in my
dream and i wake up and i'm mad at him
right yeah i think a lot of girls do
that oh my god everybody every woman
does this
you're sabotaging and like you wake up
mad and it's like it's the same thing
because
or if you think like they would do such
a thing
like it's gonna strain the relationship
it's gonna create this like
they're gonna be like why are you so why
are you being so [__] weird
like i love you what do you say to those
thoughts now like do you
because there's some parts where it's
like don't interact with them like just
kind of you can you when you see those
thoughts come up you like dude come on
get real and you can ignore it
and you can return to the present yeah
you need to just like have a
conversation with yourself be like
okay i'm aware of these thoughts and i
need to realize like what's real what's
not
and if i really want this person in my
life like because if honestly but like
if
i don't know you have to trust in your
intuition like if you want this person
in your life obviously if they love you
like yeah work hard to keep them in your
life
but except for the relationship isn't
like ideal and perfect
but that's you're gonna make me think
about
that later oh no i just planted an
intrusive thought
well no i mean you have the you have the
the
tool belt for it now though you know you
can see that it's like uh
it's it's a they're just thoughts that
that pop up and like sometimes
so me like i happen to be able to like i
was trying to figure out why i had
intrusive thoughts and so i'm like
following him back like why
why would i think that my friends aren't
actually my friends youtubed intrusive
thoughts
yeah yeah um i'm i've definitely watched
intrusive thoughts videos
um i can't recall any of them actually
well
like the first i remember like the first
video i watched oh my god it relaxed me
so much
this like this woman she was like i have
intrusive thoughts it's like a form of
ocd blah blah she's like
i want to kill my mom and i was like
what
what do you mean she starts the video
like that literally and she's like i
have like i
like detailed like images of how i'm
gonna kill her
and i'm like what the [__] like what the
[__] is going on and she's like of
course i don't want to kill her but
she's like i just have these thoughts
but i know i'm not gonna like act on
them
right and i'm like there are severe ones
like
so bad yeah and i'm like oh my god i
like it's
i get it it makes total sense to me yeah
she's like i love my mom i adore her
she's like she's my like my life
see it's it's hard though like we've got
it we have to listen to that voice that
knows that it's ridiculous like
okay you have the thought like don't now
don't define yourself with that thought
and don't beat yourself up for having
the thought
it's for me it works best when i just
kind of like brush it like i'm just like
oh there's that [__] again like i ain't
that though i know it yeah you know but
that's like even like when i start to
have like because i have panic disorder
and i'm like okay
like if i start to have the physical
symptoms to where i'm gonna like
hyperventilate and have a panic attack
i'm like i've been through this before
nice yeah even though like i know i
might have it anyways
it's like the conversation you have in
your head you're like i've had this
before
i can get through it hopefully i'm not
gonna die
but like i might i'm just kidding you
might you might always die like what
like yeah
that's an exciting thing uh i mean where
it's not like the chain you don't have
to lie to yourself basically like you
don't have to be like
i'm perfectly safe and there's nothing
that could happen like uh
just be real with yourself like if
you're anxious i just have to find like
this like
i have this it's so hard like when i do
have my panic attacks
i was very lucky to have a roommate who
understood my anxiety and like
i always wanted to call 9-1-1 because
like i thought i was dying so i was like
i need to go to the hospital
i've like been there you know i've
called 911 multiple times but like she
was like no you don't
like you don't need to do that and like
now i don't have her
and like it's it's so hard
when someone doesn't understand your
anxiety yeah and like
if you want to talk about intrusive
thoughts and they're like you're [__]
crazy dude like
you're wild but when somebody does it
like makes you feel so much better
you're like holy [__]
that's why i love having like i people
are so open on this podcast to talk
about those sorts of things with me it's
so great
i've had it who's joining us
to break down the intrusive thoughts but
i i mean because once
once you realize that like you're not
your thoughts
like and you don't have to feel bad for
the thought because like right now as
i'm talking i have no idea what i'm
going to say next
i have no idea oh yeah nobody does i
want to talk to you about something
though
talk to me about it like do you believe
in ghosts do i believe in ghosts
um i think that our perception of them
is a little confused but yes
what do you think okay well i just like
obviously i've told you i've been like
listening to like weird ass podcasts oh
man
like sleeping by myself like and like i
hate demonic [__] like i will make me
believe in this ghost i will not
watch like anything about like religion
demons like i'm so afraid of that stuff
right
right but like when we
and oh my god last night sorry i'm like
distracted
you're good okay last night i was
listening to a um
a past life regression session so like
you like
it's like a meditation session session
and like you see you lay and you like
try to remember your past lives and i
was i couldn't sleep last night i was up
to like three o'clock in the morning and
i was like
i'm gonna come back like tonight i'm
gonna do it and i'm just like try to
remember a past life
and he like tries to bring back
childhood memories
in detail and he was like i i was like
he was a thing of any childhood memory
and like i brought up like a random
childhood memory with like my dad
we were like on a four-wheeler like
pheasant hunting or something but he he
was like you're gonna remember details
you never
remembered before and it was like it
brought up so much stuff
and then he asked like do you remember
anything from your past life blah blah
blah
and like all i i just like i couldn't
get into it i wasn't like focusing
but like also we have past lives but
it's like when we die
i mean i think we have past lives but
when we die like
are there some that like are stuck in
limbo like are we haunted like are
people mad
are people upset are people happy like i
don't i totally believe in ghost stories
and like i listen to this podcast that
that tell me about like
these ghosts that have they've
encountered and i believe it 110
okay what what's that what's the podcast
about like what does it say like
like or do they like hunt them every
story every story is that when i told
you every story is different it's like a
true story radio rental um
it's like one story was about the glitch
in the matrix
like overlapping um
his girlfriend was in different moods at
the same time but he ran into them at
the same time
it was just like really i don't know
that just didn't make sense what i just
said but
there was a ghost story of this baby
it's this guy who keeps having these
vivid dreams in his twenties he keeps
having the same dream over and over
again
he was like i never had babysitters as a
kid and
he like he didn't want to talk to his
parents about it he's like it's just a
[__] dream
but he keeps having the same dream over
and over again and
the dream is that he's like has this
like middle-aged
babysitter and she's like we're gonna
play a game and he's like okay he's like
i remember being really hungry in my
dream
and he's like i just want to eat and
he's like she's like we're not gonna do
anything until we play this game
and she like turns off all the lights
and like he had like a bigger house so
like all like she would close all the
doors and she's like we're gonna play
hide and seek so she'd go hide
oh this sounds freaky already dude it's
[__] scary and like it's the same
dream so like he's like i don't even
know what to think
he like he like looks all over this
house can't find her he's like i'm
[__] hungry like
my mom's not here whatever he's like i'm
just going to go find her i know she's
going to scare me
he like goes into this room and she's
like in this like
what's that called like in a contorted
like shape
under the bed and she's like grinning at
him like with like oh
the way he explains is obviously really
terrifying of course i feel like i got
chills even just thinking
yeah and the way he actually the way he
says it and he's like i see her
and i'm like okay like i found you and
she's still grinning at me
like won't say anything and he's like
i'm like terrified
i'm scared like i'm i see you like
whatever and she like
[__] like crawls herself out of this
bed like so
fast yeah like demonic [__] and
he like sprints away from her whatever
is running running away from her and
she's like the way that she like got
like joy out of this was really creepy
he's like i keep having this dream but i
didn't want to tell my family about it
wait so it wasn't actually his mom it
was like this memory sort of
it's like a memory keeps happening and
so he's like
finally i'm like i'm gonna ask my mom
about it just to see if like we had any
babysitters he's like that i'm like
hi like i'm um putting away like
hiding from my memory whatever um
and he he has a brother and like they're
all sitting together and his mom's like
no no family like there's always family
members that babies at you like no
random person ever babies at you
whatever
and he was like getting in the car with
his brother and he's like obviously we
talk different when my mom's not around
and the brother was like i specifically
specifically
remember a woman like that being in our
house
no like it was like a [__] ghost no
dude yeah
and i'm like oh and like the way he like
tells the story he doesn't give his name
or anything he's not getting anything
he was a babysitter too like he may have
actually perceived it as being a baby
like his mom and his dad was not around
and like
it was it had to have been and he's like
it's so real and like the brother was
like so like stone cold like
he was like i remember her specifically
that's so creepy
dude i'm like they're real yeah i mean
okay so like what so what do we think
like
we just assume that they're not because
they're not like
like it's not a consistent physical
reality like it's not like
like jake and ricky like if there was a
ghost right here like it's not like a
experience hey you see it right like we
all experience it differently and we all
like
it's crazy because i feel like a lot of
these the stories are
almost remembered and it's like a
retrospect it's like it's like at the
time
you remembered it as a dream yeah that's
super cool
you know what freaks me out the most is
that like i'm not religious by any means
i believe in a higher power but i don't
know like what i believe in like if we
believe in like
demonic things like that like that stuff
we have to believe in like
higher power like heaven right like or
like a form of heaven
like a like a angelic state i don't know
like angels
i mean there's something guiding us
that's bigger than us but right and like
what but then again what i don't realize
about
or like understand about religion is
like
if we're here christianity like if we're
here like
if god doesn't want us to he died for
our sins right but if he doesn't want us
to sin
if we sin we would a hell right like if
we sin wouldn't
like the devil be happy that we sent
like wouldn't he be like yeah bro
like yeah like feeding you on yeah like
like wouldn't punish you you wouldn't be
punished for sinning that's why it
doesn't i don't understand about
religion but
i don't know you don't have to be like
religious when it comes to ghosts either
because you could
be people like it could be people like
limbo yeah dude there's so many i mean
even like the casper story that's what
it was is like they're stuck in limbo
right
we they can't move on because they have
unfinished business wasn't that like
yeah
they said that's yeah i mean i'm sure
that's not based in like a random like
what
the the movie director decided that
that's what he wanted like i'm sure
that's something
yeah there's just so many stories that
are like unexplained and there's
there's stuff out of this world that we
can't well have you have you seen that
like
so like it's official like the cia has
released paperwork saying like ufos are
real oh okay oh my god that's another
conversation
yeah i i mean they're so [__] real
they are 100 i mean
the the so it's like i i don't know if i
think they released it
like during the middle of the pandemic
which is of course
like everything is a conspiracy theory
it's impossible to talk about anything
without
yeah but it's like what do we do with
that information like what okay
like you guys like we've all seen it but
none of us in like the social
normalcy of conversation and what we do
next like we can't
like we still don't believe it like
we're saying like this is real but then
when it comes like when we're talking
about it it's like
it's still not real though it's like a
weird
but but isn't it i don't know i think it
it's got to be if they said that it's
official i mean so many people like do
they have like
alien bodies i don't know i want to know
that but
like we're one galaxy right and there's
like
millions and millions of other galaxies
infinity yeah right i don't know if
billions i have no idea
i think i think it's infinite i mean i
[__] i don't know it's all so big yeah
and like also when does like
where does space stop it doesn't right
because time keeps going
well and so what's interesting about
that too i talked with my friend brandon
um we we get like
when we go on hikes we talk about these
sort of things yeah and it's just like
this pots and pans i always say pots and
pans because i can't think about it
popping pans i love it i'm always like a
tinfoil hat that's what i say
um yeah i mean so so think about like a
microscope uh
you know you're zooming in like the
farther like what we know about like
quantum physics you zoom in and
more [__] just keeps the better the lens
gets the more stuff you can see
you just keep going deeper and the same
thing is like with telescopes
you zoom out same thing just keeps
getting more it keeps appearing it's
kind of like grand theft auto
when you like when you uncover more map
it just
have you played grand theft auto i have
also like i watched jack play it but
so you've seen like when you're at the
beginning when you haven't unlocked the
whole map
yeah you only have like this part of the
city and then you you hit the start menu
and then you can see the map
it's larger yeah yeah zelda have you
ever watched um
the first men in black yes i have okay
so when
my cousin makes fun of me because i
always like reference this but
when like it's like it's the end of the
movie and it's like the earth right and
they're like zooming out and
we end up being like a little marble
like our galaxies the marble and the
aliens are [__] playing with the
marbles like the marvel game
dude i'm like that's us like that was
your awakening
i was like six years old when i watched
that my dad made me watch it and i was
like oh my [__] god
like aliens like aliens are [__] on
this earth i know it
like [__] secret society yeah i think
that
i think that the way that okay so like
we perceive reality with our five senses
like that's like those five senses
combined
yeah but like i think that aliens are
just kind of like imagine if we were
able to
evolutionarily evolutionarily gain more
senses then we may have the ability to
see
aliens so like uh like sonar like bats
they use their two ears and they bounce
sound off of the
the walls essentially to use sonar
hearing
like it's like a new skill you get with
your senses
i feel like once we're able to like
understand aliens like maybe we'll adapt
to that
yeah maybe we're growing into being able
to even know what aliens are
yeah i mean evolution we're always
growing i want to know about it now
but like god's so real
did you ever watch do you watch netflix
yeah like um
unsolved mysteries do you watch those no
i haven't watched like it's like new
there's like
seven episodes or something it's like
about true crime
and then there's one episode it's like
the sixth episode or something like that
and it's about like a ufo story it's
like this
this i think i don't know it's like on
the east coast somewhere
and it's like multiple people had the
same experience in the same year and
it's like in the 60s
and like it was unexplainable and they
were like we got
abducted by [__] aliens and like it
there's so the people that people from
different groups of society
right so you're like there's no way that
they're live they're not plotting
together like they don't even know each
other whatever
it's like the berkshire ufo story i
think that's what it's called
if you like google it but i'm like if
people i mean like i
i really haven't really run into
somebody who doesn't believe in aliens i
don't think
i know we we all do but we all know that
it's so like taboo and strange
information yeah i don't think that yeah
because
you can't like there's nothing you could
say like well i read this article and
it's for sure true like there's nothing
that you could really be super solid
about
but it's all i mean every person has
some sort of like not personally maybe
but like some sort of
experience with some sort of alien
articles or
movie or something and they're like oh
that's got to be real or i know
there's so much to it my god it's
amazing yeah have you read the uh
or heard about the bob lazar so he was
on he was on joe rogan
i don't listen to joe rogan but i
actually like him a lot oh yeah i need
to listen to his podcast i don't i love
him though
i can send you a couple that um that you
may like i mean
he's all over aliens yeah a ton of them
he talks about aliens like there's a
there's a couple that i can send you um
where so he actually has this guy on bob
lazar who has a netflix documentary
um about working at area 51 way back in
the day
um and uh essentially like this guy
it's it's so interesting because the
more you learn about it the more this
guy is like
i don't want this to be my life like i
don't i wish i never saw it
like he's like because his life has been
like ruined from it because everybody
nobody believes him
he worked at area 51 and like did these
things
so he literally so he he he'll he's
straight up he'll talk about
um like hey i saw this at a glance like
this wasn't something that i like took a
big picture of and studied it
he would like walk by and see like i
think he said he saw like
seven different sized spaceships when he
was working there like or like
like people are working on these big
metal objects that he hasn't hadn't seen
before
he hadn't seen before they were like
rare like looking yeah they were using
they were they hired him to work on some
technol like gravity technology
that um is said to still not exist but
he had worked on it himself
but like they had a bunch of stuff where
it's kind of sad really thinking about
like he was younger
and he like did interviews and basically
said like he had his face like blacked
out and stuff and he's like here's what
i worked with here's what i saw
um he was just kind of like a nerdy guy
who
like did he sound genuine when he was
talking it's so believable it's so blue
like you like i've listened to so many
hours and hours of the guy talking and
it's like
every time he's talking he's like i
don't want it it's like this he doesn't
even want to be
he wishes this wasn't his life but it is
because he knows like how
stressful it's made his whole life like
yeah i guess he has to think about it
yeah dude the government like um and and
i again like this is a story like
i don't know it's not like i was there
but like the government was literally
like [__] with him
like they would like uh like do things
to his house
like uh he'd go inside and then like
look outside and all his windows of his
car
rolled down like like i don't know if
that's exactly what the story was but
like weird [__]
they'd like move things in his house
like just to scare him and freak him out
and it was like the government doing it
so he seemed like a crazy guy yeah he
sounds crazy
yeah yeah and so but so okay so his name
is bob lazar you should totally check
out there's a documentary on netflix and
then he's been on joe rogan and um
they kind of get into it and it's like
i don't know man like there's so much
it's we live in a world where
it's so easy for like the you know like
the wrong powers that may be to make
those people just sound like
like crazy people and like you know make
them
making them not like make the world not
want to believe them
you know but we don't really live in a
world where it's like someone's going to
be like all right here's my hard
evidence for a ufo like now what
what let's explore the galaxy i know
well what who
who like released the footage wasn't it
like the navy seals or something
yeah the navy i don't know yeah so
somebody released like radar footage
yeah i saw i saw there was another
episode of joe actually of joe rogan
where
um one of the pilots themselves actually
like came and he talked about it he's
like it was been like 25 years
yeah but he talked about the um
it was like a tick tock or tic tac
shaped object
that was like on the sonar like they
showed the radar
it was just weird stuff i mean like um
my like a couple friends my sister and
like her friends can like
account to this but we were camping like
when i was like in fifth grade something
like that
we were watching a meteor shower up and
mira lake up like ariel
like washington and we were like all
camped out
my dad was sleeping like in the tent and
like all of the girls and like
like my really good guy friend at the
time was there
and we were watching like this meteor
shower and this like little like
satellite looking thing like pops up and
it's like a tick tock it's not actually
like a tic tac shape and it's like this
like little pill looking like thing
and it was like go it would like go
really fast and stop
and like go the other direction and stop
like it was like oh it must be a
satellite i'm like what the [__] are we
crazy
and then all of a sudden it stops and
like a bunch of them like did like come
out of it
what yes and like uh [__] like
multiple like multiple people were there
all my friends can say
that's the craziest thing yeah and i'm
like like is it aliens like i don't know
like are we [__] crazy was it
satellites was it our government like i
don't know but
the way like the way it was shaped and
like the direction it was going and how
fast it was going
how close it was it didn't look like a
ufo i guess
what i mean to say but i'm like well but
think about the technology like
did it do things that like a plane we
wouldn't have been able to do in 2005 no
yeah that's like yeah like
what if even if it was excuse me even if
it was like
another what it's the russian government
testing their ufo
or or their their new like uh technology
or something
like even that is like just shows that
the government's hiding technology from
us
which is just a whole other debacle of
like should the government or like
people who are at the edge of like
technology discovering all these new
crazy [__]
should they be telling the public like
you know like but
okay so if you worked for the government
and you just like we had alien contact
like look at how we're [__] reacting
to like a reality tv show being our
president like we're we're not doing
a reality tv show is our president or
our team yeah and it's like
it's like have other countries have
contact and you know have had contact
with aliens like
they wouldn't share that no yeah like
like don't tell america they're crazy
yeah they'd [__] freak out
look at their people they're freaking
out have you seen the movie a rival
yes dude it's so good but yeah it's so
good it's
i feel like that's how it would be is
we'd be like how the [__] do we
communicate
we hope it's that way yeah have you ever
seen like
[__] what it's a bad alien movie have
you ever seen like the tom cruise alien
movie when they come down like [__]
kill a song is it like bishop the
mission impossible
isn't it like what is it oh war of the
worlds war of the world
yeah yeah so i like that movie because i
feel like uh
i like the scary the teenage boy
character how he was just kind of like a
[__] you dad sort of thing yeah he's
like you're [__] dumb
but it was good that could be how it is
though like
but i really do think like if you watch
the unsolved mystery episode
i really do think they're like studying
us they don't mean to hurt us like they
were
they cl these people claimed to be
abducted and
studied they were mostly kids mostly
and then they'd be like dropped down
into if they weren't hurt like nothing
like they remember like
split seconds of being up there but like
nothing else but their memory was erased
but i do think they're like studying us
yeah maybe we just don't really fully
understand like
they could just be humans haven't been
here for that long have you ever watched
um it's with charlie sarin
and um [__] it's about like they're
gonna go find their creators
it has has to do with like the alien
movies no way i haven't seen it i have
to google it because
it talks about
how aliens are like our creators
prometheus oh prometheus have you ever
seen that
i have seen that in 2012. yes that goes
with the alien movies right
yeah i mean i didn't know that until the
recent alien movie came out but yeah
prometheus they
go to another world and they figure out
like who me created us
like what if like somebody else dropped
us here
i mean we don't really know that i mean
like i don't know like the big bang
theory like
we like we all we all you know um
we all came from monkeys like yeah
[__] what's his name
uh terence mckinnon are you talking
about the stone deep theory
no i'm talking about the
i don't know what i'm talking about i'm
drawing a blank
well we don't we like some some people
teach us in school some people don't
because it's like controversial with
real religion
um adapting evolution evolution
right what's his name uh i let this out
because i'm so [__] dumb yeah
no i mean i don't know that's the
[__] name
who came up oh darwin theory of
evolution yeah yeah okay right yeah
that took me too long too uh dude i know
why but like
if we believed in the theory of like
evolution like
and that that yeah well dude so i heard
this thing the other day that actually
made me think i listened to this guy
called rupert sheldrake he's a
philosopher
um and he studies like he's got some
very interesting like he
he thinks like he definitely thinks
plants are conscious and these sort of
things
um thinks the son is conscious but so he
he was basically like he he said this
sentence that i was like oh wait what i
never even thought about that before
he's like we just assume that at the
beginning of the big bang theory
all of our like uh laws existed like
like
physics in time and like theory of
gravity
all existed like we don't know that
existed that long ago like
we're just assuming that those things
were all at play and we pretty much
start our base of what we know about the
universe and what we know about our
entire existence off
well we assume there was an explosion
and then we just go from there yeah and
because we can't comprehend it
we can't and like that's why we we think
that way also like [__] what the hell
what the hell happened to dinosaurs
like what really happened to dynamite
like did a meteor really come down and
kill them all no
like i don't know it's
there's so much stuff when it comes to
um have you heard of graham hancock
no jeez oh my god you need to educate me
he's another person who's on joe rogan
actually
and he is he gets to where like if you
watch too many of his videos you're like
oh he's totally crazy
like but so much [__] that he says is
just seems so true
basically he he has like kind of proven
in multiple ways that
the timeline that we read in our history
books and that like our government tells
us
is not totally true like there was like
he went to egypt
and like uh like took pictures and
measured and like studied like the
the sphinx and like the the architecture
that's in egypt
and proved that like you know certain
amount of years ago there was water
running
constantly underneath the sphinx like
he's like you can see the wear from it
this is what water does like he proved
it he's it's like
official whatever but um he proved like
basically what we know
about all of our like old timelines are
different like uh i think he has
something that
shows like the the crater holes or the
it's it's i mean it all sounds like
nonsense for sure but
essentially he had kind of proven like
the suddenness of the ice age like it
was very like weird
and crazy how sudden like the ice age
was
and i think that he had proven i could
be wrong in this that there was like
humans around
during that no way i think i could be
totally wrong but graham hancock you
gotta check him out he was on joe
but he's got he's got his own like
youtube channel and stuff too
oh my god i know and there's like
people claim like there's evidence of
ufos being like
underground in antarctica like you know
like
underground that's like the war of the
worlds whatever like they had their
ships
underground or sort the energy sources
they were there all along
yeah they were they're all along the
pilots came out and it's like you you do
wonder that
there's like so many things like even in
like even like talking about the ocean
like we only know so much about the
ocean we don't know about
yeah like what is it like 70 percent we
don't know about
yeah which is such a crazy thing too we
know more about space than we do our
oceans
that is [__] terrifying that's
craziness that is if people don't think
about the [__] i'm like
in the theory that we all agree on is
that technically we
kind of came from the ocean like or you
know like if we believe in evolution
yeah those those
things because like science right like
we have facts that's like how factual
i don't know i mean there's so much
stuff that's that makes sense
and there's so much stuff that
it's it's so hard to stick to it to
stick to one thing like i definitely
believe in evolution
i don't think that we understand
a lot of like there's some sort of
aspect of evolution that has to have
room for like
spirit or like yeah hair power
yeah like i don't want to like just like
boulder it and say like like
no because i totally believe in
evolution yeah we all came from [__]
monkeys like we did
yeah have you so have you heard the
stone nape theory no stone tape theory
is i'm probably gonna butcher this too
again it's on joe rogan um
but essentially like that when we
were monkeys we started like climbing
down out of trees for whatever reason
and we started like looking for food
sources and we started like of course
inevitably flipping over cow pies and
you find shrooms
and then essentially like the human
consciousness was formed
by excessive use of like psychedelics
no way yeah and so um and there's way
more elaborate about that too i think
there's some
some people who think that shrooms came
from comets like the first room came off
like a comet or like a an asteroid
rather
forget forget at what point it's a comet
or an asteroid but um
and then like we stumbled upon those and
we're like we ate like an alien species
of a shroom and that's what made us like
so that's
yeah you can have this conversation with
jay because she'll tell you about like
psychedelics
and like how it makes us more aware i
just had i had a reiki session with her
two weeks ago no way so did i it was an
office two weeks ago but it was like
around the time
yeah i mean what did you get out of it
um it was pretty cool
um so we did it here so relaxing oh she
got your house
yeah so she came over and we did it um
she just did a 30 minute session
and then like right away within five
minutes we sat down and had a
podcast combo like because we just
thought
that would be cool like i could try it i
was definitely stumbling over words i
was like just i felt like i was so
so tired oh god like i i had um it was
good though i had
um like within the first five minutes i
had tears for sure
um and i had a couple moments of like
like chills and like um
like like my physical body would kind of
like like vibrate and stuff
and of course they're all like
correlated with like you kind of have
thoughts come up and like kind of pass
out almost
like in a way like um you don't you
don't pass out i mean like like the
thoughts
come and it's not like you're like oh
this is for sure this thing happening
you just kind of have like interesting
like um
like you know it's a healing thing like
so she
we had spoken afterwards and and she
talked to me she's like you know things
with your father came
up and i during kind of had like a
little bit of like
kind of the thought about those sort of
things um
it's so interesting like because your
brain just really wants to understand it
but mostly i was just like i remain in
disbelief
and i and i you're you're she you're
shielding yourself from like
because you want to be skeptical a
little bit you're like because she she
is
my really good friend so i want to be a
little bit skeptical
but like she knows she knows she knows
things about my life she knows things
about you like
she knows you and but like
when she does touch you like you do feel
like sensations
and like thoughts different it's like
you unexplainable
yeah like i know what you're saying no
yeah it truly is and it's it's a you
know it's very interesting to like she'd
be at my feet
and i would feel like like my right arm
would get chills you know
like warmth in a certain space i feel
like the warmth
i think or like where the crystals were
or like where i was hurting what have
your experience has been i've only done
reiki once
with her um like we did like an hour
session and like i was just feeling like
like a vibration like warmth in certain
areas
she got like a bunch of personal things
out
but it was mainly like i think it had to
do with like my breast implants like how
i like i was like healing still
like and just like things i've been
struggling with with like my dad also
right yeah yeah i mean it's it's so
interesting i i think that
our brains are always looking for
something to
like help us out right like a release
yeah
and i think i mean it's still it's it's
nudging up against my beliefs like it's
still so new to me and i talked with her
about that too and she's
she's so cool and she's such a great
teacher when it comes to that stuff but
like
the way i see it is is you know it's
like like acupuncture
acupuncture if you're going to go like
why not try it and experience it and see
if like if you
feel better after i want to try it
actually yeah have you done it more than
once
yeah yeah what's it like in hawaii
because i used to have really bad
restless leg syndrome i don't know why i
only had it in hawaii i had it
severely yeah and i was like i'm gonna
go get something done like
not like i was like i'm gonna do
acupuncture because i had it covered
with insurance
and like it really did help with my
restless leg syndrome
so cool yeah and just relaxing yeah of
course
yeah yeah i mean and just i think just
being vulnerable like in that state like
whether it's a massage or whether it's
whatever like that's a
there's no other time in our life where
you would like do that really yeah
unless it's like a person have you ever
been like a medium no i haven't
you haven't yeah you need to do that
that's like
the big that's like the craziest
experience i've ever had
i'm going to one next week oh no [__]
i'm going to the same one i've already
seen her once
is this something that that you share or
is it something that you keep to
yourself like is it oh i share it
okay what was your first experience um
yeah i've only seen one person i've only
seen her once i'm seeing her next week
but
um i i was dating a guy at the time and
i brought him
to the to the reading and she just
she like wants to know your name but she
doesn't find out the other person's name
and i was like kind of skeptical i'm
like okay like maybe she googled me like
whatever my dad's like death was all
over the internet so i was like maybe
like she knew about him prior because
she's from woodland she lives up like
a river somewhere and
she just knew so many details about him
and like how he died and like how he
felt when he died and like who was
struggling in the family
because i have three sisters and she was
like you have three siblings
or two siblings but you're there's three
of you and i was like yeah she was like
the middle one struggling the most
and i was like oh okay i was like my
middle sister my older sister and i was
like okay yeah
i could see that and she like had these
details like where i played outside
like my childhood like she's like your
dad she your dad um
planted a cherry tree in your backyard
and i was like okay
yeah he did that was [__] weird
because she was talking about like
because he died in a plane crash and she
was like he died instantly and i was
like yeah he
i think so and like i was like maybe she
had googled that and i was like i'm like
skeptical so i'm like try not to give
her like you wouldn't know about a
cherry tree though
yeah and she was like because we had
like two acres growing up and he was
like
he he planted a cherry tree and he did
and like with cherry trees i think you
have to you have to plant
two because they can't survive without
one or like each other
and so it died yeah i didn't know that
either i asked my mom later on but she
was like yeah and like he struggled with
it and i was like oh yeah
i don't know i was like i don't know
what it looked like but it was like this
random ass plant in the middle of our
yard
and i remember i was like i remember
that and she's like we used to play
around it a lot and i was like yeah i
did that's so weird
and she moved on to like there's like
little things that she said that he's
with me like all this stuff i was like
skeptical
she moved on to like the guy i was
dating at the time and
he raced motocross and his friend had
passed away
like when he was like 15. and he had
like this necklace on under his like she
didn't know his name prior to this like
anything
she had he had his neck his friend's
necklace on he like wears his like
clothes and stuff and she's like you're
struggling with a friend of yours that
passed away
and he like wasn't giving her anything i
i didn't really know like i knew of his
friend but i didn't really know like
if it was like connecting to him and
she's like you're wearing his necklace
right now
and like he [__] turned white bro
that is that's crazy
i'm like okay and he was like yeah and
like he's skeptical too
but like he he like he's really open to
that stuff
but he was like what like what is
happening he had the necklace on
and i was like what is going on and she
was just like giving him like
advice and it was like so genuine and so
sweet
it was like ugh it was beautiful i cried
wow that's like such an incredible like
we i mean like
all cultures have always had some sort
of like shaman
or you know uh like healer or
wise knower sage you know i mean
our our society outside of religion we
don't really have like
a place for that that person and i think
that that person is still like
like maybe we can't fully comprehend
what they know yeah but they know
things that we don't some religions like
are against like mediums
and like oh yeah yeah things like that
yeah like readers
just because like they think like it's
devil work and it's sad
because like she gave me like peace a
little bit
yeah yeah honestly i'm like if i go next
week i'm like hopefully she gives me
some [__] advice like what should i
do with my life
like i don't know she's just a good like
like
person to be around atmosphere and like
even if she gave me like advice
i'd be up for it but i don't know how
much she's going to tell me
but i don't know oh that's so
interesting i feel like i would go i
would definitely go
i'm going to give you her number she's
so amazing and she has like horses and
she's just
really relaxing she's a horse girl yes
oh okay
she's like older it's different it's
different yeah it is
it's funny the horoscope joke um yeah
that's interesting i've
i've never been to a medium i mean i i
i've like i've been to others and i've
been really weird about
like i don't know how much i believe you
you know yeah
i mean again though we're always
searching for like a truth like is that
for sure true or not and it's kind of
like
there's not really like one underlying
truth about everything i don't think i
think it's like
does it resonate with you yeah how open
are you
yeah like don't you know like if it can
project you into if
if it could give you answers that like
seem to kind of fit the puzzle pieces in
your head that you've been kind of going
through
and you're like oh wow okay this person
sees a different perspective on my
situation than i do
um and you could follow it and it makes
your life a little bit better like
man why not yeah why not i listened to
um
um abraham hicks she's a channeler
um or so her name is esther hicks
but the the entity that enters is
abraham hicks
and it's it's pretty intense you know
that's more of like the immediate like
channels and stuff
yeah but um it's profound information
like a lot of times like
i'll be listening to it it's like 15 20
minutes long and there'll be like
one sentence out of the whole thing that
just like jumps at me i'm like okay i
need to hear that
you know that's always empowering
anybody like whatever
whatever kind of like feels like it's
interesting to you whatever is kind of
your intuitively like i want to try that
out like
who cares what everybody else thinks
like who cares what's like you know
right like the one truth
yeah do you believe in like past lives
i don't know i i haven't explored it too
much i mean yeah it's
you know where the way that i have an
understanding of
like what human consciousness is is like
of course we're reoccurring like of
course i believe in like some sort of
some level of consciousness
reincarnation yeah
but i don't know like how we would hold
on to the memory of our past lives
well i mean we i don't think most of us
do do you think that it's something
everybody has access to though like
through the akashic records and stuff i
mean yeah we
if we're like we're aware of it and we
open ourselves up to it
yeah but like like ah
[__] i don't know wait have you wait you
did you were talking about you did the
past life aggression did you
this is like new to me like i just like
okay like how do you experience like
when you experience data like how do you
feel
like deja vu when i experience deja vu
um do you
yeah explain to me for me it's it's this
sudden questioning like have i been here
before
and then and then it's like uh uh
have i already relived this sort of
thing um but i feel like also
for some reason i've always had your
hands yeah it's in your head yeah like
and then i i also wonder like if have i
like dreamt it before
like is like my mind like preparing
myself for this kind of situation
like i like like i try to find like a
reasonable like
explanation for it but i also
wonder if like we've known that person
in the past
have you really connected so hard to
somebody you're like i know them
i've known them like the minute you meet
them you're like i
know this person like why do i like note
this person so well
yeah i mean i i have that but for me
it's it's
like it's being comfortable yeah well
yeah i think it's selfishly is it's like
i can fully be myself with this person
it's like a
it's a country do i connect with them so
well
and like their old friend or something
yeah like the minute i meet them i'm
like
what the [__] i'm like have i met you
before but
i don't know yeah i like i tried the
whole like trying to remember my past
life but
i'm like so skeptical like i am like i
don't know about that stuff yet
so of course i mean it's hard to just
shielded because i've done
i've done um like hypnotism like i've
done like hypnotherapy and stuff and
i've done
like i want to do that like those
situations i could send you a couple um
marissa peer um she seemed to be a
pretty good one for me it's just like
very nice the way she talks it was very
trusting but um
and she and with hypnotherapy you kind
of like you kind of do
go back into those like memories that
you didn't even realize were there like
yeah like i'm like oh like i guess i
knew that that was kind of a memory but
i
never knew it meant anything to me and
it's in and she'll be like
you know exactly the memory it is you
know exactly what time of day
like you know the temperature outside
like those sort of things and you just
kind of like populate back and you
really do find yourself
thinking of that exactly like that's
what i did last night it's like he like
goes through like this
he's like you're gonna remember like a
childhood memory and like i was
remembering
like remembering little details of this
like
random childhood memory i remember like
we were on like a four-wheeler and like
there was like a like a
slit and like the four-wheeler like
four-wheeler seat i was like why do i
remember that what the [__]
and then like i remember like my dad
used to like
turn off the four-wheeler to like cruise
down to be quiet
and like i just never thought about that
it's like he like he makes you open your
eyes like little details
yeah and like i was like i'm wondering
if i like still if i listen to this for
longer
like how much i could open right i was
like six or seven at the time
so i'm like how did you did you feel
like scared at all like when you're
oh my god i feel scared i couldn't sleep
last night so i was listening to this
and i was like well [__] no wonder
you couldn't sleep last night you're
talking about past life no i was like
listening to that [__] stupid
scary podcast and i was like oh my god
i'm listening like past life stuff i was
like oh my god i'm so woke
i was like 2 a.m i couldn't sleep and i
was like i'm just gonna like listen to
my past life and like
i kept like seeing like images in my
head like [__] up images i'm like what
the [__] i don't even know what this is
about like i don't i
like i'm [__] weird dude like i'm
with you i do all the same [__]
now you're having intrusive alien
thoughts yes i'm like [__] abduct me
like study me
check me out yeah i want to know like
drop me off later but like tell me
what's wrong with me also
like what's up like i want to see you i
want to see what you look like yeah like
if there's going to be a huge abduction
like
say they take they won't be huge they'll
take a few have you ever watched the
fourth kind
no i don't think so it's like a scary
movie you need to watch that later the
fourth kind yeah
is it is it scary or suspenseful i mean
both it's not scary to some people but
it's like suspenseful enough to spook
you but it's about like
alien abductions they think it's alien
abductions but in juneau alaska
like you have to like fly there or fly
to get to this town i guess
i don't i'm not sure how it goes but um
like random people have gone missing
and like they all went to the same
counselor because it was a small town
and they were all having the same
nightmares
oh [__] that's weird dude yeah and like
imagine being a counselor you'd be like
oh
and her and eventually the counselors
like
like little girl got kidnapped and she's
never been found
and they think that she's crazy like
whatever dude she like i don't know how
real this [__] movie is but like
i believe in the stuff i'm like dude
[__] alien abductions
they're like reading like going into
their mind and like making you crazy
i mean what if okay so elon musk says
that
we like we are
organic bootloaders for ai he says
sentences like that which is like oh
[__] like
so what if we are like we kind of are
the alien thing
like it's just like humans what humans
grow into
like in the future yeah but like when we
grow into that
it's a this is such a thought experiment
this might sound so crazy
but i love it what if like what we grow
into
is actually kind of like aliens like we
grow into
like our understanding of what that is
it's not that we become something
different than we are
it's just that evolution keeps doing
what evolution does
yeah and we grow into like an
understanding of like
different dimensions and different
versions of consciousness and different
like
the forms are what we see in our because
we see physical form in our five senses
but maybe
watching like the matrix or like you
watch rick and morty
i love ricky oh [__] i love rick and
morty like
to get high and watch rick and morty but
what's another like
glitch in the matrix type thing like
interstellar
yeah interstellar it's this incredible
movie there was a
radio rental the podcast okay let me
tell you this [__] story i mean
okay i don't know how good i'm gonna
tell it you can you can edit this out
but this girl like this guy and this
girl they just moved to new york it's
like 2011 2010 whatever
they're like they're like [__] hyped
up they moved to a new city
they're like they have jobs going to
college whatever they go to like an
engagement party they get drunk like not
that drunk they like go home like sleep
he like wakes up at noon his
girlfriend's out there it's not that
weird because like she has a crazy job
she goes into meetings and stuff
whatever
he's like i'm gonna go out he's gonna
make some breakfast make coffee go out
for a smoke
he's like in new york city like um
manhattan or something like that he's
like downtown he's like smoking a
cigarette
he hears like heels coming towards them
it's his girlfriend she like shoves him
she's yelling at him she's like [__] you
can't believe you would do that to me
and he's like the first thing i noticed
she was wearing like some [__] crazy
ass outfit like she had like
clubbing clothes on and he's like it's
noon he's like what are you wearing
he said what are you doing and he's like
what did i do like i'm so
like what do you mean like he's like so
confused she's like going up she's like
walking past him
going to the door typing in the code the
like the code to the building
goes in she has a purse he's like
following her he's like what did i do
and she's like you know you [__] did
she's like mad at him whatever
she takes out a set of keys like
younique's had a keys opens up the door
and he's like what the [__] is going on
and she's packing up her [__] she's like
i'm [__] leaving you we're breaking
up
like everything was great like the night
before like they were so happy he's like
it was like the highlight of our life
like they were so happy to be in a new
city
and he's like what the [__] did you like
did you go through my phone like did you
like
like misunderstand something and she
packs like a bag of like a bunch of
clothes
and she like picks up a plant like
throws out the tv breaks the tv breaks
the plant whatever
leaves he follows her she gets in the
cab drives away
he's on the street and he's like my
girlfriend's broke with me what the [__]
four seconds later
his girlfriend's like wrapped around his
like waist he feels like a
woman wrapped around his waist four
seconds later after she gets in the cap
and he's like what the [__] and he's
like like he's like who is this
and it's his girlfriend different
clothes like hunky-dory like
in a great in a great [__] mood and
she's like
true story and she's like what's going
on like what's wrong
she's like i just got off work like blah
blah and he like doesn't say anything
and he's like
like and she's like what's going on with
you how can you make sense of like
he's like thinking to himself and he's
like am i like how do i have to like
sign my like put myself insane asylum
like do i am schizophrenic
like that's what i'm thinking in my head
like as i'm listening to this he has
nothing to gain by like telling the
story he's not telling his name he's not
like
telling like much detail and
he's like the first thing i'm gonna do
i'm gonna go see if the apartment's
[__] up so he runs up to the apartment
the door is like slightly cracked and
everything is like broken
and he's like okay i'm not crazy it
happened he's like but what if i did
that
he's like he's like what if i did that
and or that's what i thought i was like
what if he like [__] did that he
opened the door with the keys
because he remembers specifically her
opening at the door with the keys right
cause he said he locked the door like to
go get a smoke and
she's like the girlfriend comes in she's
like bawling she's like do we get robbed
like what's going on like what the [__]
they look at the security tapes and
there was a girl that looked identical
dude yes that's terrifying
[__] up okay a glitch in the matrix
how long ago was this what was this
2012 2011 2010. and
like it was like cct cc tv or whatever
so like you couldn't really like
it was exactly what he described he was
like this girl came in she had a [__]
set of keys like
she opened the door i didn't open the
door for her well she knew the code too
you said
yeah so they saw that so like she like
because they called the cops her dad was
like a cop or something like that
and they um because she was like were
you cheating on me or was this a girl
that had a key
like yeah and she
or what happened like they caught the
cops did fingerprints
because like they were so it was her dad
that did it and the only fingerprint
prints that were on the door was
the girlfriend and the boyfriend that's
[__] crazy
like what do you what if that was the
only interaction you ever had like that
in like the rest of your life you're
just like hopefully that doesn't happen
again
i know and it's like i was like maybe
the girlfriend's crazy but like how
because he's like
she was in a cab when that my other when
the other
happy girlfriend walked up she was like
i could see the cap
he's like i don't know there's no way
she could have snuck out of the cab
and he went to like uh like a psychology
team i don't even know what he like a
professor and he was like
it was like a glitch in the matrix like
it could be like overlapping realities
and i was like there's no way how it's
like why is the first
story i've heard i don't know i'm just
like i believe him because he's so
genuine when he tells the story he's not
gaining anything by telling the story
right well it's like i was saying with
that bob lazar guy like it's like it
doesn't make his life better to say hey
i saw aliens because like
imagine like having to live the rest of
your life like the majority of people
think you're crazy
yeah he's like i told like five people a
story and they're like bro you're
[__] weird that's a cool story but
you're weird
yeah and he's like he legit he was so
sad he legitimately thought he was crazy
i mean you would never be able to forget
about that also like i would question my
like
sanity i'd be like am i crazy like or is
my girlfriend crazy
yeah or somebody playing tricks on me
does she have an evil twin sister
this is what i think about like okay
think about dudes like kanye west the
poor guy like
oh my god i feel so bad for him i want
to give him a hug so bad i know i wish i
could hug him too
like right now of course it's this is
just going through it for sure but like
i remember i was listening to an
interview and he was like he was
sensible in the interview he's like
i honestly thought that like people were
putting brain microchips in my head like
he was like
thinking those level of things but
imagine if you see one
crazy alien weird situation like that
the rest of your life you're gonna be
like cool that's probably [__] real
like oh my god how do you determine
between your intrusive thoughts and your
like
regular thoughts also yeah like if you
see something crazy like that you're
gonna be like everything's [__]
[__] up crazy
yeah like are you are you the alien
version of my girlfriend
or ah well maybe though maybe
god i don't know maybe we just don't
understand our reality as much as we
think we do
i mean i don't know like
but maybe maybe i don't know i i went on
reddit because i was like i need to like
that's where you get the answers i'm
sorry i get the answer like yeah true
crime like
if you ever want to like learn about
true crime stories i go and read it but
i they're like maybe she had a twin a
girl that looked like her that took
advantage of the situation because it's
2011. i have no idea
oh right yeah but like the professor he
went to
if you listen to the podcast it makes
more sense than i explain it but
he's like i understand it it's like
overlapping realities but
i was like i don't know how much of that
i believe i like made my sister listen
to it last night and she was like i
don't know
like he does sound genuine but okay
which one's that one more time i think i
want to listen to that one
radio rental radio rental episode two
like if there's
a couple there's a couple stories in
each
yeah episode so the site i like those
too because i feel like they've been
doing a good job i don't know if they
did it
did it on this one but they um like on
the spotify like
those like short stories they tell yeah
they do like a lot of cool like sound
effects
oh my god it makes you so scared yeah
yeah it's so cool i've listened to like
i listened
on the way and i was like so terrified i
was like oh my god
it was about mental illness but like
that's very explainable
right but i'm just oh it's so scary so
sad
yeah some some are some stories are
scary and like you can't explain but
some are just like
sad tragic right i mean i i enjoy just
learning about them because
i love that edge of like our knowledge
where
we're like flipping the switch off and
on of like dude do i believe this or not
i know i love that
like i think it's so cool it helps with
my anxiety i'm like relaxed
right yeah you're exploring what because
because you kind of what you end on
is kind of this like comfort and not
knowing you're like
yeah i really don't know and it's kind
of reminder of like
i don't really know a lot of this stuff
like that you know life is so
so crazy in so many different layers
like you can't know all the truths and
all the reality
you know so true or is it
i don't know where is it um we're
getting up here
pretty well in time my friend okay um i
got to take a leak so
oh my god so do i well it's about that
time so let's send them off i appreciate
you talking about
aliens and ufos and alternate realities
and uh uh
breast implants and politics sadly
i mean i started us out with the mask so
it was a great combo though i appreciate
you coming on and talking about it um
can we just send off um one little
just piece of advice like that maybe
through like the breast implant
situation that the
um that you've learned like because i
always say so shaylee always says
think about what would what would a
young jake like 16 year old jake
what would he need to hear like what
would be some [__] that would that that
would
help him at 16. so what what do you have
for like younger people who are like i
want to get breast implants or i want to
change my body yeah if i was if i could
tell my younger self
i would just be like you know health as
well
no um health is most important and um
just like i don't know it's cliche but
love your body how it is
sad but it's yours
it's yours yeah and it's um you know
if you cut yourself open you can't take
it back and it's really
sad yeah to know that
well i really appreciate you coming here
and sharing like such a personal story
like you know of course like
especially when you when you had to go
through you know mental things like it's
all horrific it's all terrible to have
to go through like these pains and stuff
but
you know it's hard to speak about when
you went through like
mental health stuff so i really
appreciate you coming to talk about
thanks for having me
yes of course listener take care of
yourself stretch
drink some water do some pilates do some
yoga do something take care of
yourselves
have a good day ahoy guys i hope you
enjoyed the episode whatever app you're
on if you don't mind just hitting follow
or share
or review or star or heart or whatever
it is on the app
just interact with it just share it with
somebody just give me a review give me a
something i appreciate it i'm glad that
you guys take
the time to listen to anything that me
or anybody that i know has to say
it's fantastic also whatever you're
doing right now
just get present don't let yourself just
keep listening to a bunch of
other podcasts don't let yourself just
do a bunch of more youtube videos
get outside and stretch go start working
on that thing that you want to be
working on start chipping away at your
dreams just
do 10 minutes of it just get present
follow your heart
see you later see you next episode next
week peace
[Music]
you